Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is not how I wanted this evening
to go.
I know how you wanted this evening
Believe me
this is better.
Who are you working for?
Lermentov, yes?
Does he think
we have to go through him
to move our cargo?
I thought General Solohob
is in charge of the export business.
Solohob
a bagman, a front.
Your outdated information betrays you.
The famous Black Widow
and she turns out to be
simply another pretty face.
You really think I'm pretty?
Tell Lermentov we don't need him
to move the tanks.
Tell him he is out.
Well...
It's for her.
You listen carefully
Who are you?
Get out!
There is sickness here!
My father's not waking up!
He has a fever and he's moaning
but his eyes won't open.
Slow down.
My father...
Like them?
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-