Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
PROFESSOR X: The future.
A dark, desolate world.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER PA CONTINUES)
PROFESSOR X: A world of
war, suffering, loss...
on both sides.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
Mutants and the humans
who dared to help them.
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
Fighting an enemy
we cannot defeat.
(MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER PA)
(PANTING)
PROFESSOR X: Are we
destined down this path?
Destined to destroy ourselves
like so many species before us?
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Or can we evolve fast
enough to change ourselves?
Change our fate?
(DISTANT GROWLING)
Is the future truly set?
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(WHIRRING)
(MUFFLED THUMPING)
They're here!
(PANTING)
Time's up.
WARPATH: Sentinels!
Sunspot!
KITTY: Let's go.
(PANTING)
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
WARPATH: Run!
(GRUNTING)
BLINK: Go!
(WHISTLING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(CHOKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
Blink! No!
(MOANS)
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROARING)
(YELLS)
(GROWLS)
(ROARING)
Too late, assholes.
(MAN SOBBING)
Don't move, you mutant scum!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
No!
Flat on the ground,
hands behind your head!
(MAN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
PROFESSOR X: So few of us left.
KITTY: Professor?
I've found them.
(POWERING UP)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
BOBBY: Professor!
Bobby.
Hey, Storm.
Hey, kid.
KITTY: Professor,
you made it.
Whenever the Sentinels attack,
Warpath spots them...
then I send Bishop
back to warn us
of the attack before it happens.
Blink scouts the next site...
and then we leave before they
ever know we were there.
Because...
we never were.
What do you mean
you were never there?
She projects Bishop back in time
a few days to warn the others...
of the coming attack.
So she sends
Bishop back in time?
No, just his consciousness,
into his younger self.
His younger body.
Wow.
This might just work, Charles.
What might work?
The Sentinel program
was originally
conceived by
Doctor Bolivar Trask.
In the early '70s, he was one of the
world's leading weapons designers.
But, covertly, he had begun
experimenting on mutants...
using their gifts
to fuel his own research.
TRASK: This is extraordinary.
PROFESSOR X: There was one mutant who
had discovered what he was doing.
A mutant with the ability to
transform herself into anyone.
Mystique.
PROFESSOR X: I knew her as Raven.
We met when we were children,
grew up together.
She was like a sister to me.
I tried to help her...
but only succeeded
in driving her away.
She hunted Trask
across the world.
And at the Paris
Peace Accords in 1973,
after the Vietnam War...
she found Trask...
and killed him.
(GUNSHOT)
It was the first
time she killed.
It wasn't her last.
But killing Trask did not have
the outcome she expected.
It only persuaded the government
of the need for his program.
(GASPS)
PROFESSOR X: They captured her that day...
tortured her,
experimented on her.
In her DNA,
they discovered the secrets
to her powers of transformation.
It gave them
the key they needed...
to create weapons that could
adapt to any mutant power.
And in less than 50 years...
the machines that
have destroyed...
so many of our kind were created.
(LOW GROWL)
But it all started
that day in 1973...
the day she first killed.
The day she truly became...
Mystique.
You want to go back there.
If I can get to her,
stop the assassination...
keep her out of their hands...
then we can stop the Sentinels
from ever being born.
And end this war
before it ever begins.
Uh, I can send someone
back a couple weeks.
Maybe a month.
But you're talking about
going back decades.
You have the most powerful brain
in the world, Professor...
but the mind can only stretch
so far before it snaps.
It would rip you apart.
I'm sorry.
No one could survive that trip.
What if someone's mind
has a way of snapping back?
What if someone can heal as
fast as they're ripped apart?
STORM: Okay, spread out.
BISHOP: Take your positions.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
So I wake up in my younger
body, God knows where.
Then what?
You'll need to go to
my house and find me.
Convince me of all of this.
Won't you be able
to just read my mind?
I didn't have my powers in 1973.
Logan, you're going
to have to do for me
what I once did for you.
Lead me, guide me.
I was a very different man then.
You'll have to be patient with me.
(LOGAN SCOFFS)
Patience is my strongest suit.
You'll need me as well.
What?
After Mystique left Charles,
she came with me...
and I set her on
a dangerous path.
A darker path.
It's going to take the two
of us, side by side...
at a time when we couldn't
be further apart.
Great.
So where do I find you?
Well, it's complicated.
Basically, your body
will go to sleep
while your mind
travels back in time.
As long as you're back there,
past and present will
continue to coexist.
But once you wake up...
whatever you've done will
take hold and become history.
And for the rest of us, it will
be the only history that we know.
It will be like the last
50 years never happened.
And this world, and this war...
the only person who will
remember it is you.
All right, Logan...
I need you to clear your head
and to stay as calm as possible.
What? What do you mean?
If your mind gets rocky, it will
be harder for me to hold you...
and you could start to slip
between past and future.
What if I need to
get a little rocky?
Think peaceful thoughts?
Peaceful thoughts...
Do you have any good news?
Well, you don't really age,
so you'll pretty
much look the same.
BOBBY: You won't have
much time in the past.
The Sentinels will find us.
They always do.
And this time,
we won't be able to run.
We'll have no escape.
This is our last chance.
You really think this will work?
I have faith in him.
MAGNETO: It's not him I'm
worried about, it's us.
We were young...
we didn't know any better.
We will now.
See you all soon.
This might sting a little.
(SCREAMING)
(SOFT '70s SONG PLAYING)
The first time
Ever I saw your face
(WATERBED SLOSHING)
Whoa.
I thought the sun
Rose in your eyes
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
And the moon and the stars
Were the gifts you gave
LOGAN: Holy shit.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
It worked.
Hey, what's going on?
Gwen, get dressed.
LOGAN: Who the hell are you?
Hey, I don't know
what's going on.
You're supposed to be
guarding the boss's daughter,
not screwing her.
Well, I didn't sleep with her.
MAN: No?
No.
I mean, yes, I slept
with her many times.
Jimmy!
That wasn't me.
That was the old me.
I just got here 20 seconds ago.
MAN: Really?
Then what happened
to your clothes?
My... Oh.
Would you believe
me if I told you
I was sent here from the future?
Huh?
(CHUCKLES)
Get out of here, sweetheart.
Yeah.
We're gonna take care of this comedian.
LOGAN: No, you're not.
You're gonna give me the keys to
your car and some money for gas...
or you're gonna wake
up in the hospital.
Trust me, I know how
these things play out.
Oh. Because you're
from the future?
No.
Because of these.
MAN: What the hell?
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROANS) God damn it!
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BULLETS CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
Peaceful thoughts.
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
SENATOR BRICKMAN: We are reviewing
all of our defense expenditures...
and all the black books
are being opened.
We can't support a weapon
that targets our own citizens.
If these mutants,
as you describe...
are already living among us...
then they are living
here peacefully.
PARKER: We haven't had an
incident in over 10 years.
After what happened in Cuba?
PARKER: That was
never confirmed.
We have very real
enemies out there...
the Russians, the Chinese.
We are talking about
a tenth of a tenth...
of a tenth of our population.
Allow me to read
something to you.
Please.
This was acquired by
our friends at the CIA.
It's a dissertation...
written by a mutant
at Oxford University.
And I quote...
"To Homo Neanderthalensis..."
"his mutant cousin,
Homo Sapiens..."
"which is us..."
"was an aberration."
"The arrival of the mutated
human species, Homo Sapiens..."
"was followed by the immediate
extinction of their less evolved kin."
Well...
Now, we are the Neanderthal.
Speak for yourself,
Dr. Trask.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLES)
You know, when you sent our
soldiers to Vietnam...
without the weapons they
needed to win the war...
you underestimated your enemy.
(CHUCKLING) You do that
with this enemy...
Mmm...
and it won't be some border
skirmish halfway around the world.
This time, the war will
be for our streets...
our cities, our homes...
and by the time you see the
need for my program...
it will be too late...
and you will have lost
two wars in one lifetime.
We are sorry,
Dr. Trask...
but your Sentinel Program...
it ain't gonna fly.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Can I help you, Colonel?
Just here to give our
boys a proper send-off.
I'm sorry, sir, but we have orders.
This is a quarantined area.
Stand aside, soldier.
That's an order.
SOLDIER: Atten-hut!
At ease.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What is all this?
Lab reports, blood tests.
It's all getting packed up
and shipped back.
Where is it going?
Same place they are.
Trask Industries.
STRYKER: Let's go, gentlemen.
I'm taking you out
of this shit show.
HAVOK: Shipping home?
Not just yet.
What are you doing with those?
Something to make the ride
a little smoother.
I'm transferring you
to a private facility...
where we can run
a few more tests.
(COLONEL SANDERS
CLEARS THROAT)
Your men are not military.
Private outfit.
We're authorized
to remand these men.
Hmm.
These troops are going home.
Well, Colonel, I don't believe you
have jurisdiction in this matter.
I'm afraid I do, son.
I'm sorry, who are you?
The question is, Major...
...who are you?
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
Raven!
That's not my name.
(GRUNTING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY) I had that.
I know.
Let's move out.
Come on, let's go.
HAVOK: Where's Erik?
I'm on my own now.
Let's go! Move it!
(SOLDIERS
YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
Hold that plane!
Wouldn't wanna leave these boys
in this godforsaken country.
SOLDIER: Yes, sir.
You're not coming
with us, are you?
My war's not over.
The enemy is still out there.
The four privates,
where did they go?
They were headed
towards the tarmac.
Can I help you?
Uh... Yeah, what
happened to the school?
The school's been shut for years.
Are you a parent?
(SCOFFS) I sure as hell
hope not. Who are you?
I'm Hank. Hank McCoy.
I look after the house now.
You're Beast?
Look at you. I guess
you're a late bloomer.
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but I'm gonna have
to ask you to leave.
(GRUNTS)
So where's the Professor?
There's no professor here.
You're pretty strong
for a scrawny kid.
You sure there's not
a little Beast in there?
No, he's not here.
Come on, Beast.
Come on, Beastie.
No.
(GRUNTS) Hey!
I said the school's closed.
You need to leave. Not
until I see the Professor.
There's no professor here,
I told you that.
Look, kid. You and I are
gonna be good friends.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
You just don't know it yet.
Professor!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Professor!
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(HANK ROARS)
(LOGAN SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
CHARLES: Hank?
What's going on here?
Professor?
Please don't call me that.
Why?
You know this guy?
Yeah, he looks
slightly familiar.
Get off the bloody
chandelier, Hank.
(GLASS CLINKING)
You can walk.
You're a perceptive one.
I thought Erik...
Which makes it
slightly perplexing that
you missed our
sign on the way in.
This is private property,
my friend.
I'm gonna have to ask him
to ask you to leave.
Well. (SIGHS)
I'm afraid I can't do that...
because I was sent here for you.
Well, tell whoever it was
that sent you that I'm busy.
That's gonna be
a little tricky...
because the person
who sent me was you.
What?
About 50 years from now.
Like in the future,
50 years from now?
Yeah.
I sent you from the future?
CHARLES: Piss off.
If you had your powers, you'd
know I was telling the truth.
How do you know
I don't have my p...
Who are you?
LOGAN: I told you.
Are you CIA?
No.
You've been watching me?
I know you, Charles.
We've been friends for years.
I know your powers
came when you were 9.
I know you thought you were
going crazy when it started...
all the voices in your head.
And it wasn't
until you were 12...
that you realized all the voices
were in everyone else's head.
Do you want me to go on?
I never told anyone that.
Not yet, no, but, you will.
All right,
you've piqued my interest.
What do you want?
We have to stop Raven.
I need your help.
We need your help.
I think I'd like to wake up now.
(SIGHS)
What does she
have to do with this?
CHARLES: So you're saying...
they took Raven's
power, and what?
They weaponized it?
Yep.
She is unique.
Yeah, she is, Hank.
LOGAN: In the beginning, the Sentinels
were just targeting mutants.
Then they began to identify the
genetics in non-mutants...
who would eventually have mutant
children and grandchildren.
Many of the humans tried to help
us, but it was a slaughter.
Leaving only the worst
of humanity in charge.
I've been in a lot of wars.
I'd never seen
anything like this.
And it all starts with her.
Let's just say
for the sake of...
the sake, that I
choose to believe you...
that I choose to help you.
Raven won't listen to me.
(SIGHS)
Her heart and soul
belong to someone else now.
LOGAN: I know.
That's why we're
gonna need Magneto, too.
HANK: Erik?
(LAUGHING)
You do know where he is?
Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
He's where he belongs.
You're just gonna walk out?
Ooh, top marks. Like I
said, you are perceptive.
The Professor I know would
never turn his back...
on someone who'd
lost their path.
Especially someone he loved.
You know...
I think I do remember you now.
Yeah. We came to
you a long time ago...
seeking your help.
And I'm gonna say to you
what you said to us then.
Fuck off.
Listen to me, you little shit.
I've come a long way, and I've
watched a lot of people die.
Good people. Friends.
If you're gonna
wallow in self-pity...
and do nothing, then you're
gonna watch the same thing...
you understand?
We all have to die sometime.
Told you there was
no professor here.
What the hell happened to him?
HANK: He lost everything.
Erik, Raven...
his legs.
(SIGHS) We built the school,
the labs, this whole place...
then, just after
the first semester...
the war in Vietnam got worse.
Many of the teachers...
and older students were drafted.
It broke him.
He retreated into himself.
I wanted to help,
do something...
so I designed a serum
to treat his spine...
derived from the same formula that
helps me control my mutation.
(SIGHS) I take just enough
to keep myself balanced...
but he takes too much.
I tried easing him back...
but he just couldn't bear
the pain, the voices.
The treatment
gives him his legs...
but it's not enough.
He's...
He's just lost too much.
(SIGHS)
YOUNG RAVEN: You're
not scared of me?
YOUNG CHARLES: I always believed I
couldn't be the only one in the world.
Charles Xavier.
Raven.
You're hungry and alone.
Take whatever you want.
We've got lots of food.
You don't have to steal.
In fact...
you never have to steal again.
And that's a promise.
CHARLES: I'll
help you get her.
Not for any of your future
shite, but for her.
Fair enough.
But I'll tell you this.
You don't know Erik.
That man is a monster.
A murderer.
You think you can
convince Raven to change?
To come home?
That's splendid.
But what makes you think
you can change him?
Because you and Erik sent
me back here together.
HANK: The room
they're holding him in
was built during
the Second World War...
when there was
a shortage of steel.
So the foundation is pure
concrete and sand. No metal.
CHARLES: He's being held...
a hundred floors
beneath the most
heavily guarded
building on the planet.
LOGAN: Why is he in there?
What, he forgot to mention?
(SNICKERING)
Uh, JFK.
He killed...
(CHUCKLING)
What else explains a bullet
miraculously curving through the air?
Erik's always had
a way with guns.
Are you sure you want
to carry on with this?
This is your plan, not mine.
HANK: We don't have any
resources to get us in.
CHARLES: Or out.
It's just me and Hank.
I knew a guy.
Yeah, he'd be a young man now.
Grew up outside of D.C.
(CHUCKLING)
He could get into anywhere.
I just don't know how the hell
we're gonna find him.
Is Cerebro out of the question?
We have a phonebook.
I thought you'd be getting
ready for your trip, sir.
I just came to
grab a couple files.
Is that a new scarf?
It's nice.
Thank you.
(BEEPS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(GASPS)
Dr. Trask?
One second.
Oh.
We added some names
to the Paris meeting.
Thank you.
Is something wrong, sir?
No. It's nothing.
Would you mind
typing up my itinerary?
I don't wanna miss anything.
LOGAN: Here, here, here.
CHARLES: Where?
Just stop here.
All right, all right.
Next time I'm driving.
Don't get used to it.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(MAN TALKING ON TV)
(SIGHS) What's he done now?
I will just write you a
check for whatever he took.
We just need to talk to him.
Peter! The cops
are here. Again.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(PLAYING PING-PONG)
PETER: What do
you guys want?
I didn't do anything.
I've been here all day.
Just relax, Peter.
We're not cops.
Of course you're not.
If you were,
you wouldn't be
driving a rental car.
How did you know
we've got a rental car?
I checked your registration when
you were walking to the door.
I also had some time to kill
so I went through
your rental agreement.
Saw you were from out of town.
Are you FBI?
No, you're not cops. Hey, what's
with this gifted youngsters place?
That's an old card.
He's fascinating.
He's a pain in the arse.
What, a teleporter?
No, he's just fast.
And when I knew him
he wasn't so... young.
PETER: Young?
You're just old.
So you're not afraid
to show your powers?
What powers? What
are you talking about?
Do you see
something strange here?
Nothing anybody would
believe if you told them.
(ARCADE GAME PINGING)
So, who are you?
What do you want?
LOGAN: We need your help, Peter.
For what?
To break into a highly
secured facility...
and to get someone out.
Prison break?
That's illegal, you know.
Um...
Well, only if you get caught.
So, what's in it for me?
You, you kleptomaniac, get
to break into the Pentagon.
How do I know I can trust you?
Because we're just like you.
Show him.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
That's cool,
but it's disgusting.
TOUR GUIDE: Built in 1943, the Pentagon
is the world's largest office building...
housing more than
25,000 military employees...
stretched over six
million square feet.
Where's the bathroom?
GIRL: He always needs to pee!
(ALL LAUGH)
(STATIC CRACKLES)
(DOOR BUZZING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Yeah, we're getting broadcast
signal down here. What's going on?
Damn it, call Maintenance,
get them down here.
(CHUCKLES)
(SHOES SQUEAKING)
(VIBRATING)
(RUMBLING)
(ALARM BLARING)
...fought for and captured the island
of Iwo Jima from the Japanese Empire.
Now, this month-long battle...
included some of
the fiercest fighting
during World War
II in the Pacific...
(CHEF SPEAKING FRENCH)
(ALARM BLARING)
(GRUNTS)
ERIK: In three seconds, those
doors are going to open...
and 20 guards will
be here to shoot us.
I know. That's what
I'm waiting for.
What are you doing?
I'm holding your neck so
you don't get whiplash.
What?
(SLOWLY) Whiplash.
GUARD: Don't move!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GROAN)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
PETER: You're
good, it'll pass.
It happens with everyone.
You must have done
something pretty serious.
What did you do, man?
What did you do?
What did you do? Why'd
they have you in there?
For killing the President.
Ah. Wow.
(WHISPERS) Shit.
The only thing I'm guilty of
is fighting for people like us.
You take karate?
You know karate, man?
I don't know karate.
But I know crazy.
(CHUCKLES)
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and
girls, this is a Code Red situation.
We are evacuating
the entire floor...
so that my associate and I...
can, uh, secure the prison.
Who are you?
We're special operations, CB...
FB-CID.
Perhaps you didn't hear me
when first I spoke...
but it is imperative
that you understand...
we're in a complete
lockdown situation.
We have to get you
to the third floor...
(GRUNTS)
Oh, I'm sorry.
Were you finished?
(GRUNTING)
They told me you control metal.
"They"?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
You know, my mom once knew
a guy who could do that.
I'm sorry, I'm just not
very good with violence.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Charles?
(GRUNTS)
(CHARLES GROANS)
Good to see you too, old friend.
And walking.
No thanks to you.
You're the last person in the
world I expected to see today.
Believe me...
I wouldn't be here
if I didn't have to.
If we get you out of here,
we do it my way.
No killing.
No helmet.
I couldn't disobey
you even if I wanted.
I'm never getting
inside of that head again.
I need your word, Erik.
Nobody move!
Hold it right there!
Charles.
GUARD: Don't move.
Hands up, or we will shoot!
Freeze them, Charles.
I can't.
Hands up!
(CLATTERING)
No!
(MELLOW '70s SONG PLAYING)
If I could save time in a bottle
The first thing
that I'd like to do
Is to save every day
Till eternity passes away
Just to spend them with you
If I could make days
last forever
If words could make
wishes come true
I'd save every day
Like a treasure and then
Again,
I would spend them with you
But there never seems
to be enough time
To do the things you want to do
Once you find them
I've looked around
enough to know
That you're the one I want
to go through time with
(ALL GRUNTING)
(ALARM CONTINUES RINGING)
Thanks, kid.
CHARLES: Peter,
thank you very, very much.
You take care.
PETER: Hey, I saw your
flight plan in the cockpit.
Why are you going to Paris?
Imagine if they were metal.
CHARLES: Do me a favor and return it for me.
Okay.
And, Peter?
Take it slow.
(CHUCKLES)
Where did they dig you up?
You're gonna find
this hard to believe...
but, uh, you sent me.
You and Charles.
From the future.
(SIGHS)
How did you lose them?
The treatment for my
spine affects my DNA.
You sacrificed your powers
so you could walk?
I sacrificed my powers
so that I could sleep.
What do you know about it?
I've lost my fair share.
Ha.
Dry your eyes, Erik.
It doesn't justify
what you've done.
You have no idea what I've done.
I know that you took the things
that mean the most to me.
Well, maybe you should have
fought harder for them.
If you want a fight, Erik...
LOGAN: Sit down.
...I will give you a fight!
Let him come.
You abandoned me!
You took her away...
and you abandoned me!
Angel.
Azazel.
Emma.
Banshee.
Mutant brothers and sisters...
all dead!
(GRUNTS) Countless others...
experimented on.
Butchered!
Erik!
Where were you, Charles?
We were supposed
to protect them!
Where were you when your
own people needed you?
Hiding! You and Hank!
Pretending to be
something you're not!
Erik!
You abandoned us all.
(SIGHING)
(PANTING)
So, you were always an asshole.
(SCOFFS)
I take it we're best
buddies in the future.
(CHUCKLES)
I spent a lot of years
trying to bring you down, bub.
How does that work out for you?
You're like me.
You're a survivor.
Do you wanna pick
all that shit up?
(FRENCH DISCO MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
General, maybe you should slow down,
we have a big day tomorrow.
We're celebrating, captain. It's not every day you win
a war, let alone against the American devils.
I'm getting another bottle.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Excuse me.
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
I'm pretty sure it was my fault.
You speak Vietnamese.
I'm an interpreter.
I speak many tongues.
Let me buy you another drink...
unless you're here with someone.
I'm alone.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
A bottle of Johnnie Walker please.
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
You're going to the Summit tomorrow?
A pretty girl interested in politics...
Looks can be deceiving.
Lady.
Show me more, baby?
Clothes off?
What's the matter, baby? You don't
think I look pretty like this?
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(CHOKING)
(GASPING)
(SQUEAKING)
(SNORING)
Fancy a game?
It's been a while.
I'm not in the mood
for games, thank you.
ERIK: I haven't had
a real sip in ten years.
(SIGHS)
(SWALLOWS)
I didn't kill the President.
The bullet curved, Erik.
Because I was
trying to save him.
They took me out before I could.
Why would you try and save him?
Because he was one of us.
(SCOFFS)
You must think me so foolish.
We've always said they
would come after us.
I never imagined they'd
use Raven's DNA to do it.
When did you last see her?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
The day I left for Dallas.
And how was she?
Strong.
Driven.
Loyal.
How... How was she?
She was...
We were...
I could see why she
meant so much to you.
You should be proud
of her, Charles.
She's out there
fighting for our cause.
Your cause.
The girl I raised was
not capable of killing.
You didn't raise her,
you grew up with her.
She couldn't stay a little girl
forever, that's why she left.
She left because you
got inside her head.
That's not my power.
She made a choice.
But now we know where
that choice leads, don't we?
She's going to murder Trask,
they're going to capture her...
and then they're
going to wipe us out.
Not if we get to her first.
Not if we change
history tomorrow.
I'm sorry, Charles...
for what happened.
I truly am.
It's been a while since I've played.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'll go easy on you.
Might finally be a fair fight.
You have the first move.
The diplomats from
all around the world
are arriving here
today at the Hotel Royal.
It's an historic day.
It's the, uh, official ending
of the United States' military
involvement in Vietnam.
There we have the South
Vietnamese Foreign Minister...
with other South
Vietnamese dignitaries.
The Summit doesn't begin
for another hour.
The hotel has arranged
a private room
upstairs for
your special guests.
TRASK: That will be
plenty of time.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Good afternoon, everyone.
Hello, thank you for coming.
Congratulations on
winning this war.
Now, I know you all
have hands to shake
and photos to take downstairs...
so I will get
right to the point.
There is a new enemy out there.
An enemy that will render
your arsenals useless...
your armies powerless...
and your nations defenseless.
TRASK: You will need a new weapon for
this war. I call them Sentinels.
Named after
the ancient guardians
that stood at
the gates of the citadel.
(GRUNTS)
They have the aeronautic
capabilities of a Harrier jet.
Armed with guns
that can fire off...
more than 2,000 rounds per minute
of thermoceramic ammunition.
But size, power, speed...
you could find that
at Lockheed or Boeing.
No, what makes the
Sentinels so special...
is the ability to target
the mutant X-gene.
A genetic guidance system
that can lock onto a mark a half a
mile away. (SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
It won't trigger unless it
has identified the target.
With this weapon, there will be
no human collateral damage.
If I turn it on, the system
couldn't even activate in here.
(BEEPING)
Unless there's a mutant.
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
There has to be
some kind of mistake.
My machines don't make mistakes.
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
What are you?
(MAN SPEAKS VIETNAMESE)
I assure you...
TRASK: No, don't shoot it.
I assure you,
I don't know what
you're talking about.
(SPEAKING VIETNAMESE)
(GRUNTING)
ERIK: Raven!
(GRUNTS)
Raven? Raven!
(SHUDDERING)
Raven?
(BEEPING)
Charles?
We've come for you, Erik and I.
Together.
RAVEN: I never thought
I'd see you again.
CHARLES: I made you
a promise a long time ago
that I would protect you.
(GRUNTING)
MAN: Wolverine!
(GASPING)
CHARLES: I'm going
to keep you safe.
I'm going to keep you
out of their hands.
Erik?
What are you doing?
Securing our future.
Forgive me, Mystique.
As long as you're out
there, we'll never be safe.
Erik...
Use your power,
Charles. Stop him.
He can't.
(CROWD GASPING)
(GROANING)
KITTY: He's slipping back.
I'm losing him.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(ALL GASPING)
LOGAN: Stryker!
STRYKER: Someone will finish
what we've started, Wolverine!
One day!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Restrain him.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
Erik!
Where am I?
Huh?
How the hell did I get here?
What? You came to us.
Who are you?
Charles.
Charles Xavier!
I don't know you.
Huh?
What the hell is that?
Whoa.Whoa. Look, I can deal with this.
Just go.
Stop Erik!
Erik, please...
I'm sorry.
Erik...
(CROWD SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
You're Logan, that's Hank
McCoy, I'm Charles Xavier.
You spent the last
couple of days with us.
You're on acid.
Somebody gave you
really bad acid, yeah?
(RATTLING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
Just hold on tight,
we'll get through this together.
(KITTY GROANS)
Oh, my God, Kitty.
She's wounded pretty bad.
(GROANING)
(CLAMORING)
(ROARING)
(KITTY WHIMPERING)
I got him.
(GASPS)
Professor?
What happened to you?
I just saw someone who's gonna
bring me a lot of pain someday.
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
Where's Raven?
Gone.
What?
We have to get out of here.
We want to know if there's
any sort of connection with...
(ALL CLAMORING)
Yesterday,
the Paris Peace Summit...
was rocked by the appearance
of unidentified assailants...
the likes of which
the world has never seen.
Mass hysteria has gripped
the nation as people ask...
"Where did they come from?
Will they be back?"
And most importantly,
"Are they friend or foe?"
That was London
correspondent Toby Elliot...
reporting from the
Paris Peace Summit yesterday.
What the hell are we dealing with here?
Off the record.
Two days ago, this
man, Erik Lehnsherr...
escaped from a maximum security
prison inside the Pentagon.
We believe that this woman
is a former associate
of Lehnsherr's.
They were together in Cuba,
the day of the crisis in '62.
He was also implicated
in Kennedy's assassination.
What about that thing?
MAN: We don't know what
that thing is, sir.
Actually, we really don't
know what any of them are.
Yes. Yes, we do.
They're mutants.
He has the power
to control metal.
Last I checked, that's what
most of your weapons
were made of.
And she can transform
into anyone.
A general, a secret serviceman.
Even you,
Mr. President.
She could walk
into this office...
and order a nuclear strike
if she was in the mood.
And that's only two of them.
Do we have any countermeasures?
Any defense?
I was waiting for you
to ask me that question.
That's an experimental program, sir.
Strictly off the books.
(DOG BARKS)
You're telling me these mutants
are out in the world...
and our best defense
are these giant metal robots?
Many of the mutants
look like us.
My Sentinels can
tell the difference.
I have eight prototypes
ready to go.
They're built out of
a space-age polymer,
not an ounce of metal on them.
I want to make a demonstration.
I want the world to know
that we can protect them.
What do you need to get
these things operational?
I already gave that
number to Congress.
Unfortunately, they
elected to shut me down.
It's going to cost a bit
more to turn them on.
NIXON: Whatever you need.
TRASK: Oh,
and one more thing.
If we do manage to capture
them, I would like her.
For research purposes,
of course.
(NEWSREADER SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Terrible thing.
What is?
Being born like that.
Is it?
Can you imagine...
Looking in the mirror and seeing that
staring back at you?
Yes, I can.
Where do you think she comes from?
You think she has a family?
Yes.
She does.
(NEWSREADER SPEAKING
FRENCH ON TV)
(BEGGING IN FRENCH)
If I see so much
as a screw move,
I will jam this
into your throat.
How did you find me?
You taught me well.
It's been a long time
since we were this close.
I missed you.
You tried to kill me.
So the rest of us could live.
What do you mean?
We received a message
from the future.
Don't lie to me.
I never have, and I never will.
Humans use your blood,
your genes,
to create a weapon
that wipes us all out.
I was only doing what I thought
necessary to secure our future.
So what's to stop me
from killing you
right now and
securing my future?
Nothing.
It doesn't matter anymore.
They have your DNA. Your
blood was on the street.
Whose fault was that?
Mine.
I've seen their plans.
They're creating a weapon.
And now they have what they
need to take it further.
We have to strike now, while
we still hold the upper hand.
I've seen too many
friends die, Erik.
I don't want a war.
I only want the man
who murdered them.
This is war.
What happened to you?
Did you lose your way
while I was gone?
Are you still Charles' Raven?
Or are you Mystique?
Trask is the enemy.
Killing one man isn't enough.
It never was for you.
Goodbye, Erik.
(GRUNTING)
LOGAN: What happened?
Come on.
Can he walk?
He needs his treatment.
Hank, I can hear them.
I know. It's okay.
Can you make it stop?
I'll get them.
(GROANS)
LOGAN: Hey, hey.
Pull yourself together.
It's not over yet.
(PANTING)
You don't believe that.
How do you know?
CHARLES: As these go...
this comes back.
They all come back.
Look.
I'm still here...
and she's still out there.
We need your help, Charles.
Not like this.
I need you.
We can't find Raven.
Not without your powers.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
HANK: I added a little extra
because you missed a dose.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Charles.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Hank, do me a favor.
Would you help me
to my study, please?
Come on, I got you.
(CHARLES GRUNTS)
Are you sure about this?
Absolutely not.
TRASK: This creature
is extraordinary.
Her genes could hold the key
to mutation itself.
I need more.
That's all they were able to
scrape off the pavement in Paris.
More than blood.
I need brain tissue...
spinal fluid, bone marrow.
Imagine...
Sentinels that could transform,
adapt to any target.
If I could just get
my hands on her.
This girl could leap
the program forward years...
decades into the future.
How old is your son now, Major?
Jason?
He's coming up on ten now,
if you can believe it.
Eight years from fighting age.
And how many of
our sons and brothers
did we just ship
home in body bags?
Maybe fifty,
fifty-five thousand?
And how many more
on the other side?
Never before...
in all of human history...
has there been a cause which
could unite us as a species.
Until now.
You really hate,
mutants, don't you?
On the contrary,
I rather admire them.
The things they can do.
I see mutants as our salvation.
A common enemy.
A common struggle
against the ultimate enemy.
Extinction.
I believe our new friends...
are going to help us
usher in a new era, Bill.
A new era of genuine...
and long-lasting peace.
MAN OVER PA: Attention, attention.
Transport departure
in two hours.
Repeat. Transport
departure in two hours.
(SIGHS) When was the last
time you were down here?
The last time we went
looking for students.
A lifetime ago.
(ELECTRICAL WHIRRING)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE: Welcome, Professor.
(SIGHING)
HANK: Raven's wounded.
She won't be moving fast.
(BLOWS)
These are muscles I haven't
stretched in a long time.
(GASPS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WEEPING AND YELLING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING
CONTINUES)
(GROANING)
Charles!
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Charles? It's all right.
(PANTING)
I'll go check the generator.
It's not the machinery, is it?
I can't do this.
My mind...
Yes, you can.
(STAMMERING) It won't take it.
You're just a little rusty.
You don't understand. It's not
a question of being rusty.
I can flip the switches.
I can turn the knobs.
But my power comes from here.
It comes from...
And it's broken.
I feel like one of my students.
Helpless.
It was a mistake
coming down here.
It was a mistake freeing Erik.
This whole thing has
been one bloody mistake.
I'm sorry, Logan, but they
sent back the wrong man.
You're right.
I am.
Actually, it was
supposed to be you.
But I was the only one who could
physically make the trip.
And, uh...
And I don't know
how long I've got here.
But I do know that
a long time ago...
actually, a long
time from now...
I was your most
helpless student.
And you unlocked my mind.
You showed me what I was.
You showed me what I could be.
I don't know how
to do that for you.
You're right.
I don't.
But I know someone who might.
Hmm.
Look into my mind.
You saw what I did to Cerebro.
You don't want me
inside your head.
There's no damage you can do...
that hasn't already
been done. Trust me.
Come on.
(SCREAMING)
Hey.
Hey, Logan.
Hi, Jean.
Kill me.
I love you.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
You poor, poor man.
Look past me.
No, I don't want your suffering.
I don't want your future!
Look past my future.
Look for your future.
That's it.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Charles.
(CHUCKLES)
So this is what becomes of us.
Erik was right.
Humanity does this to us.
Not if we show
them a better path.
You still believe?
Just because someone
stumbles, loses their way...
it doesn't mean
they're lost forever.
Sometimes we all need
a little help.
Oh, I'm not the man I was.
I open my mind...
and it almost overwhelms me.
You're afraid,
and Cerebro knows it.
All those voices...
so much pain.
It's not their pain
you're afraid of.
It's yours, Charles.
And as frightening
as it may be...
that pain will
make you stronger.
If you allow
yourself to feel it...
embrace it...
it will make you more powerful
than you ever imagined.
It's the greatest
gift we have...
to bear their pain
without breaking.
And it's born...
from the most human power.
Hope.
Please, Charles...
we need you to hope again.
Find what you were looking for?
HANK: The power's
back on.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
(GRUNTS)
(METAL CLANKING)
(ELECTRICAL WHIRRING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WIND HOWLING)
(MOANING)
BOBBY: She's lost
too much blood.
She can't keep going like this.
We have no choice, Bobby.
We can wake him up.
No!
They need more time.
I had...
a glimpse into the past.
If we wake Logan now...
we may set our fate
on an even darker course.
They need more time.
(SIGHS)
(KITTY GROANING)
(WOMAN ANNOUNCING
IN FRENCH OVER PA)
Raven, stop.
Stop running.
Charles?
Where are you?
Back at the house...
where you should be.
I need you to come home.
I know what I need to do.
If you kill Trask...
you will be creating countless
more just like him.
Then I'll kill them, too.
Those are Erik's words,
not yours.
Oh!
The girl I grew up with
wasn't capable of killing.
She was good...
fair, full of compassion.
I have compassion.
Just not for Trask.
He's murdered too many of us.
Shut her down, Charles.
Get in her head.
CHARLES: She's
not letting me in.
I'm barely holding on.
I'm not strong enough yet.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(GASPS)
I know what Trask has done...
but killing him
will not bring them back.
It will set you on a path...
from which there is no return.
An endless cycle of killing.
Us and them, until
there is nothing left.
But we can stop it,
right now, you and I.
You just have to come home.
I have to?
You haven't changed
at all, Charles.
Like I said...
I know exactly
what I have to do.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Where is she?
(CHUCKLES) She's in an
airport, boarding a plane.
LOGAN: A plane to where?
CHARLES: Washington, D.C.
Guys, there's something
I need to show you.
We're going backwards in time.
I set the system I designed...
to record any news about Paris
over all three networks...
and PBS.
All three? Wow.
Yeah, and PBS.
Look what I found.
Tomorrow, in front
of the White House,
the President will
make his announcement.
He will be joined by Secretary
of Defense Laird...
and has even sought the help of
renowned scientist Bolivar Trask...
his special advisor
to combat this mutant issue.
The White House has asked...
CHARLES: Raven
doesn't realize...
that if she kills Trask
at an event like that...
with the whole world watching...
Then I came a long way
for nothing.
HANK: And there's more bad news.
I saw in a report...
they found traces
of her blood in Paris.
For all we know,
they already have her DNA...
which is all they'd need.
To create the Sentinels
of the future.
There's a theory
in quantum physics...
that time is immutable.
It's like a river. You can
throw a pebble into it...
and create a ripple, but the
current always corrects itself.
No matter what you do, the river
just keeps flowing
in the same direction.
What are you trying to say?
What I'm saying is...
what if the war is inevitable?
What if she's meant
to kill Trask?
What if this is just
simply who she is?
Just because someone
stumbles, loses their way...
doesn't mean
they're lost forever.
(CHUCKLES)
No, I don't believe
that theory, Hank.
And I cannot believe
that is who she is.
Ready the plane.
We're going to Washington.
You all right?
Getting there.
(SIGHS)
Whatever happens today, I need
you to promise me something.
You've looked into my mind
and seen a lot of bad...
but you've seen the good, too.
The X-Men.
Promise me you'll find us.
Use your power,
bring us together.
Guide us. Lead us.
Storm. Scott.
Jean.
Remember those names.
There are so many of us.
We will need you, Professor.
I'll do my best.
Your best is enough.
Trust me.
(WIND HOWLING)
There's 12 carriers
inbound, 10 miles!
They've found us.
REPORTER: Thousands of people
will be gathered here today.
They've come from
all over the world...
to witness history,
along with news crews...
from at least 50
different countries.
Thank you.
(BEEPS)
Can I see your
invitations, please?
Yes, you may.
These two are with me.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
CHARLES: Logan!
SECURITY OFFICER: Please, this way, sir.
(INDISTINCT VOICES IN HEAD)
I haven't found her yet.
But she has to be here.
ANNOUNCER: The President
of the United States.
(PATRIOTIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
My fellow Americans...
today we face the gravest
threat in our history...
mutants.
(VOICES RESUME)
We have prepared
for this threat.
(INDISTINCT VOICES IN HEAD)
In the immortal words
of Robert Oppenheimer...
"Behold."
"The world will never be
the same again."
(PATRIOTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Can I help you?
No, you can't.
(STATIC)
Here they come.
(INDISTINCT VOICES IN HEAD)
RAVEN: This is for you,
brothers and sisters.
Raven?
I have her.
(WITH RAVEN'S VOICE)
Let me go, Charles.
There. You see?
Secret Serviceman.
Left of the stage.
Got him.
CHARLES: Go.
(SENTINELS POWERING UP)
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't tell you
to activate them.
I didn't.
(CROWD GASPING)
CHARLES: Raven,
please, listen to me.
We've been given a second
chance to define who we are.
Don't do this.
Gentlemen, you cannot
pass this point.
We can't stop that many.
No, but we can slow them down.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SCREAMING)
Erik!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Ah!
(PANTING)
Storm!
(GROANS)
(SNARLS)
(YELLING)
Go, go, go!
(MEN CLAMORING)
MAN: Watch your head!
(SIRENS WAILING)
MAN 1: Go, go, go!
MAN 2: Take us to DEFCON 3.
Mr. President,
we are Code Red.
MAN 3: What's our air
defense readiness?
MAN 2: All our air
defenses are ready one.
NIXON: What the hell
happened out there?
I will fix it.
You said that before.
I wanted to make a statement.
Now the whole goddamn world
knows we can't protect them.
TRASK: I will fix it.
NIXON: You damn well better.
(GRUNTS)
(CROWD SCREAMING)
Charles!
No, no, no...
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(FEMALE DISPATCHER SPEAKING
OVER RADIO)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(BOTH PANTING)
STORM: Is everybody okay?
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
No!
Behind you.
Ah!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
COLOSSUS: Now!
(SCREAMS)
(SUNSPOT SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
HANK: I'm probably not supposed
to ask this kind of thing...
but in the future, do I make it?
No.
But we can change that.
Right?
(ROARING)
Do what you were made for.
(GRUNTS)
Where are you?
Ah!
(GROANS)
(ROARS)
I got this! Go!
(LOGAN COUGHS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Oh, dear God, no.
(SCREAMING)
So much for being a survivor.
(GASPING)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(ALARM RINGING)
(DETECTOR BEEPING)
One of them is in here.
(MEN SHOUTING)
TRASK: No, no, no!
Don't kill it!
I need it alive.
(RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
What the hell has happened?
(METAL CREAKING)
(ALL GROANING)
(INHALING)
(GROANS)
You built these
weapons to destroy us.
Why?
Because you are
afraid of our gifts.
Because we are different.
Humanity has always feared
that which is different.
Well, I am here to tell you...
to tell the world...
you are right to fear us.
We are the future.
We are the ones
who will inherit this earth.
And anyone who
stands in our way...
will suffer the same fate
as these men...
you see before you.
Today was meant to be a
display of your power.
Instead I give you a glimpse...
of the devastation my race
can unleash upon yours.
Let this be a warning
to the world.
And to my mutant brothers
and sisters out there...
I say this.
No more hiding.
No more suffering.
You have lived in the shadows...
in shame and fear for too long.
Come out.
Join me.
Fight together in
a brotherhood of our kind.
A new tomorrow...
that starts today.
(GROANS)
MAGNETO: All those years wasted...
fighting each other, Charles.
To have a precious
few of them back...
(RUMBLING)
(BANGING)
(GROANS)
MAN: Mr. President, sir.
Stand down.
I said, stand down!
You want to make a statement?
Kill me. Fine.
But spare everyone else.
(GRUNTING)
Very heroic,
Mr. President...
but you had no intention...
of sparing any of us.
The future of our
species begins now.
(GUNS COCKING)
(BEEPING)
(GASPING)
You used to be a better shot.
Trust me, I still am.
Get out of my head, Charles!
Raven.
Please, do not make us
the enemy today.
Look around you.
We already are.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
CHARLES: Not all of us.
All you've done so far...
is save the lives of these men.
You can show them a better path.
Shut her down, Charles.
I've been trying to control you
ever since the day we met...
and look where that's got us.
Everything that happens now...
is in your hands.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I have faith in you, Raven.
(SCREAMING)
(EXHALES)
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
RAVEN: He's all
yours, Charles.
(GRUNTS)
If you let them have me,
I'm as good as dead.
You know that.
I know.
Goodbye, old friend.
Goodbye, Erik.
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
(SIGHS)
HANK: Are you sure you
should let them go?
CHARLES: Yes.
I have hope for them.
There's going to be a time,
Hank, when we are all together.
HANK: What about Logan?
(SOFT '70s SONG PLAYING)
The first time
(GROANS)
Ever I saw your face
I thought the sun...
(BELL RINGING)
KITTY: Buckminster Fuller is a
great example of an architect...
whose ideas were very similar
to those of a utopian future.
Good morning, Logan.
Late start. (CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Have a good lunch.
Good job.
STUDENT: Thank you.
STORM: Very good job.
LOGAN: Storm.
Jean.
Hey, Logan.
Are you okay?
You're here.
Where else would I be?
Whoa.
Easy, pal.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, some things never change.
It's good to see you, Scott.
Uh-huh.
See you later, Jean.
Professor.
Logan, is everything all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is.
You did it.
Did what?
Logan, don't you have
a class to teach?
A class to teach?
History.
History?
Actually, I could use
some help with that.
Help with what?
Pretty much
everything after 1973.
I think the history I know
is a little different.
Welcome back.
It's good to see you, Charles.
It's good to see everyone.
Well...
I had a promise to keep.
You and I have a lot of
catching up to do.
Yeah.
What's the last thing
you remember?
Drowning.
CHARLES: The past.
A new...
and uncertain world.
CHARLES: A world of
endless possibilities.
And infinite outcomes.
You kidding me?
Oh, he's alive!
(COUGHS)
CHARLES: Countless
choices define our fate.
Each choice, each moment...
a ripple in the river of time.
What do you want us to do
with him, Major Stryker?
CHARLES: Enough ripples...
and you change the tide.
I'll take him from here.
CHARLES: For the future
is never truly set.
(CROWD CHANTING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/rym6
Help other users to choose the best subtitles