Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Don't move.
I told Batroc...
If we want to make
S.H.I.E.L.D. pay us...
start sending them bodies now!
I have a bullet for someone...
Move that foot... you want
a bullet in the head...?
I don't like waiting.
Call Durand.
I wanr this ship ready to
move when the ransom comes.
Start the engines.
Shut up.
You want to be a hero? Is that it?
All right, I've
waited long enough...
Find Batroc...
If I don't hear anything
in two minutes...
I start killing them!
I'll find him.
Two minutes.
Radio silence from
S.H.I.E.L.D., Batroc...
Time is up.
Who dies first...?
You!
Get that one.
The line just went dead.
I've lost contact with them...
I thought you were more
than just a shield...
Let's see.
I have her. Find him.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org