Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This job
We try to save as many people as we can.
Some times it dosen't mean everybody
But you dont give up
New York
Washington DC
Sukovia
OKAY, that's enough
captain people are afraid
That's why i'm here
We need to be put to check.
Whatever form that takes, i am game
i am sorry Tony!
Because seeing the situation to south i cant ignore it
Sometime's i wish i could
Sometimes i wanna punch you in your perfect teeth
i know i am not perfect
But the safest hands are still our own
"Rohd"
i was Wrong about you
Whole world is wrong about you
They are coming for you
i am not the one that needs to watch their back
This dosen't need to end in a fight TONY
You just started a WAR
Stay down Final WARNING
I can do this ALL Day
Alright i have run out of patience "UnderRoos"
Hey Everyone.......
Made By : Madmax 12
Hey guys plz Rate
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7e6fu
Help other users to choose the best subtitles