Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
(MUSIC PLAYING)
JASON: So I said,
"If opposing counsel's
"invoking fiduciary
liability precedent
"under the terms of
Landgraf v. Henson,
"Your Honor, please,
by all means, go ahead,
"rescind the plaintiff's
de facto petition
"for injunctive relief."
(ALL LAUGHING)
It was fun. It was fun. Yeah.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
I'll be right back.
DAVID: So funny.
"Injunctive relief."
That tickled my funny bone.
What's up, Nick? (SIGHS)
Fucking sucks dick
about Grandma, huh?
Yeah.
Old woman fucking
murdered like that.
Nick, she had cancer.
That's what they
want you to think.
She had cancer for 10 years.
A little too convenient, Jason.
No, it's not, at all.
We'll never know the truth.
We absolutely know the truth.
Yeah.
Grandma had cancer
for 10 years.
You don't just die
from cancer, Jason!
It's a conspiracy, man.
Just like 9/11.
Oh, God.
For your information,
Grandma is not right here.
Grandma is gone and she
was taken from us.
And we must find the man that did this.
Nick! Nick!
Stop it. Ow, man!
There are Rockport's.
Fuck, man. I just got these.
(NICK SCOFFS) Calm down...
I'll see you at the
crossroads, Grandma.
What are you doing? Are you kidding me?
Right now?
Hey, get your shit together!
My dad and my fiancee
are literally standing
right next to us.
Beyonce's here? No.
Your dad and fiancee are
saying yes to Beyonce?
What? No.
Is Jay-Z here, too? No, Nick.
Is Blue Ivy here? Nick. (SIGHS)
I'm in the minority. I think
their kid's gonna be hot.
(INHALING)
What is that? Hmm?
What are you doing? I'm just...
Are you fucking high right now?
No, this isn't...
You're high as a kite!
It's an e-cigarette.
It's filled with a little weed,
but it's an e-cigarette.
Grow up, man!
What are you doing?
"Grow up"? How adult are you?
What, do you listen
to NPR in your Volvo?
You play racquetball
competitively
against business associates?
No. No.
You ever go away to a rented
house with other couples
and then play Scattergories
over a bottle of white wine?
Jason.
(STAMMERS) Uh...
(EXHALING)
I just blew a shot
at your grandma's memory.
Nick, get it together, right now.
(INHALES)
Lock it up.
I'm not hugging you.
If I hug you, will you
stop messing around?
(SCOFFS)
(BLOWING)
(GASPING)
Crop-dusted, motherfucker.
You just got crop-dusted.
You're high now.
Hey. Get the fuck away from me.
Now we're both high at Grandma's funeral.
(COUGHING)
We're bonded for life.
Uncle Dave, I'm sorry, man. It's a
tough day. (CONTINUES COUGHING)
(FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
Poor Grandpa...
Our first reading
is from Deuteronomy 30:19.
"This day, I call
the heavens and the earth
"as a witness against you..."
(SIGHS)
"...that I have set before you
life and death..."
Hey, babe, I found the tie
you're going to wear
to the rehearsal brunch Sunday.
Do you like the coral
color or the salmon?
"...that the race
is not to the swift..."
(WHISPERS) Either one.
"...nor the battle
to the strong."
Babe, what's wrong?
Coral or salmon?
Well, what do you like?
I mean... I like the coral.
That's what
I was going to say, too.
Okay, cool. Okay. Okay.
Coral it is!
It's going to be a special day.
"...now choose life,"
"so that you and your
children shall live."
Anyway, I'm down
in Valdosta right now.
I opened up
a fucking pet shop...
Not pet shop, "puppy mill."
Puppy mill...
You know, designer dogs
get a bad name,
but they can go
for quite a pretty penny.
Really? It's just hard
to get them to mate.
Oh. Because the little dogs,
they don't wanna
fuck the big dogs,
and the big dogs, they don't
wanna fuck the little dogs...
So I got to manually
do it, you know. Oh.
I got to spread
and manually shoot in.
Uh-huh. So, what's up with you?
Well, I'm keeping
pretty busy...
Cool. Hey, Aunt Diane,
how's it going? Hi, Nick.
Hey, Nick.
I just don't understand
why you have to drive
down to Florida,
tomorrow already, Dad!
We just had the funeral.
Your grandmother
and I were there
at this time every year.
It's what
she would have wanted.
I'd drive down myself,
except they took
my license away.
But why does Jason have
to be the one to drive you?
He's so busy at work...
Got the wedding
coming up next weekend,
the rehearsal brunch.
You know, the entire law
firm is coming to this.
It's true, Grandpa. Jason...
We have a lot of stuff, Meredith and I...
I'll handle it.
JASON: Go ahead.
How about Cousin Nick?
Huh, Dad?
Why doesn't Nick do it?
We got this chocolate Lab
down at the store
that is just so horny,
every time I touch
the back of its ear,
it just gushes cum.
Uh, okay. I mean,
like a squirting...
Is that your dog?
Nick isn't legally allowed
to leave the state
of Georgia anymore.
I've barely seen this guy
since high school.
What's wrong with spending
some time with him?
Oh, so spending time
with family
is suddenly important
to you now?
Look, he can come here tomorrow
morning for breakfast.
We can drive down
to Boca during the day,
maybe play a round
of golf or two,
then he'd be back here
in Atlanta the next day.
He can't just
flake off for two days!
The risk versus reward
here is just...
I don't see it happening.
(SIGHS) It's what she would
have wanted, that's all.
But if you have to get
ready for your wedding,
if you're that busy...
I just don't understand
why he wants you to take him.
You're not even that close.
Well, we used to be.
Grandpa and I got along
growing up.
We used to build these
model trains every Christmas,
so I brought him...
Well, it seems like
we're cutting it
a little close here, you know,
with the rehearsal
brunch on Friday...
I know. I know.
And by the way,
I can't find any
of the Martha's Vineyard
vacation photos
for the slide show. (SIGHS)
I'm just freaking out.
That's because
they're on my laptop,
which I've got right here.
So I'll send them
to the wedding planner.
You don't have to worry
about anything.
Thanks. Oh, and your dad says take
75, because 16 takes forever.
Yeah, I know. He's got
it all mapped out for me.
And can you take
my car, sweetie?
Uh, I need
the SUV for the wine.
(EXHALES)
(1950s MUSIC PLAYING)
Grandpa?
(CLATTERING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
Grandpa?
(WOMAN MOANS)
(COUPLE MOANING)
Hey! You made it! (SCREAMS)
Give me a minute...
(WOMAN MOANING)
Oh, God! Shit!
WOMAN: (ON TV) Grab my ass!
You ready to hit the road?
I'm really sorry, Grandpa.
(STAMMERING) I didn't think
you'd be doing that.
Ah, so you caught me
taking a number three.
Big deal, right? Number three?
Have a drink.
Uh... No. I'm driving, so...
I just got to finish up
my exercises,
and then we'll hop on 16 to 95.
Dad says we should take 75 to 95.
It's more direct.
Dad's full of shit.
Grandpa, are you
sure you're okay?
Thanks for doing this,
by the way.
Those fuckheads down at the DMV
took my goddamn license away
because of these fucking
cataracts in my eye.
But I can still hit the shit
out of a golf ball,
that's for sure!
I made a tee time
for us in Florida
for this afternoon.
You can use your
grandmother's lady clubs,
they're right there
by the front door.
Okay.
All right, you ready?
I thought the plan was
to have breakfast here?
That's your breakfast.
Now let's go get in that
giant labia you drove up in
and get the fuck out of here.
You sure I should be driving
with this, Grandpa?
Don't worry, if you spill it,
this giant tampon we're
driving in should soak it up.
Just finishing a work email
for the Steinhart file...
So you're a lawyer at your
dad's firm now, is that right?
That's right,
and Meredith is too.
You know, her dad is one of
the managing partners
there, so...
I know, that's... Yeah.
It couldn't have
worked out better.
Because it's just
that I remember
when you were in high school,
you told me how much you
wanted to be a photographer,
travel the world.
That sort of thing.
You remember when
I got you that subscription
to Time magazine?
Yeah, I used to be into
photography, but, um...
I mean, with Dad being
at the firm, pfft,
it just made so much more sense
to focus on
a college curriculum
that stressed
the law school track.
I mean, I love what I do,
Grandpa.
Being a corporate lawyer
is awesome,
I get to handle
SEC compliance...
No shit! Yeah. Yeah.
You handle SEC compliance?
LP agreements.
Oh, man, I didn't know that.
LLC agreements.
You're shitting me!
Being a corporate lawyer,
it's got its upsides.
You know what I'd rather do?
What?
I'd rather let Queen Latifah
shit in my mouth
from a fucking hot air balloon.
That's me. I'm gonna hit the
liquor store over there,
get some more of the creature.
Meet you back
at the Dildomobile in five.
You're paying the check,
Alan Douche-owitz.
(DOOR OPENS)
Where do I know that guy from?
He looks so familiar.
He looks like
Abercrombie fucked Fitch.
Mmm, yeah,
while J.Crew J'd-off.
Shit! No, you guys, he was...
It's so funny.
He was my lab partner
in photography class,
freshman year.
No shit! He's a Florida alum?
Lenore, you can totally
finish the trifecta.
Oh, my God, I already
have alum, remember?
I fucked that crying
divorced guy, Tony.
With the big balls.
Right. Yeah.
In the porta-potty. Yeah.
At the tailgate. Yeah.
I need a professor.
Wait, I'm sorry.
What's the trifecta again?
It's this thing I read about
where in my senior year
I have to fuck a freshman,
an alumni, and a professor.
Where did you read that?
In my diary.
Hmm.
Where I wrote it... Yeah.
He used to take the most
beautiful portraits
without using any filters
or Photoshop...
LENORE: I've read your diary.
SHADIA: He was amazing.
BRADLEY: Oh, my God, you did?
Yeah.
BRADLEY: Did you like it?
You guys aren't listening. I'm
gonna go say hi to him. Okay?
Cool. Slut...
I hope you don't get
Tommy Hilfingered.
That was really late,
but it still counts.
Just like all my periods...
Ew. What?
Hi. How are you?
Good. Here you go,
you can keep the change.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not... You...
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Um...
Guys? Guys, listen to me.
What?
Let's go. Bitch, what?
Shut the fuck up! Go!
Oh, my God!
Wait a minute.
You all set? (DOOR OPENS)
Yeah, I just gave my money
to the other waitress, sorry.
There is no other waitress.
I'm the only one who's
ever worked here. Ever...
Shit! The fucking piece
of shit car never starts!
Hey!
God, he's like
a Mitt Romney Terminator.
Excuse me!
Uh, sorry, my shift is
actually over, so... Sorry...
Oh, no way. What?
I know you. No.
Yeah, I do. You were
in my photography class.
You took all those
landscapes. Right?
Shadia.
Yeah. Shadia.
Holy shit, you're Shadia?
Yeah. Shadia. Shadia.
Jamba! (EXCLAIMS) What the fuck!
Shadia. It means
"singer" in Arabic.
Or in ancient Arabic,
"al-munshida
alati tunadi lel-mei."
Or, "she whose name
calls others to water."
That's actually right.
Uh, Shadia, this is my...
Dr. Richards. I teach history
at the University of Georgia.
You're a professor?
Yeah. Why? You looking
for some extra credit?
Jason and I are doing
a story on the Middle East.
He's a photographer
for Time magazine.
You know, I lost my virginity
at my pop-pop's bingo night.
My name's Lenore.
Ah! "The rare
and radiant maiden"
"whom the angels named Lenore."
"Quoth the Raven, 'Nevermore.'."
Diplomaticos, huh?
Hey, you know your cigars.
What are you,
half Cuban or something?
Actually, I am, Professor.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
The bottom half. Okay.
SHADIA: Okay, yeah, we're
heading out. Yeah.
Good to see you. We're going
to Daytona Beach for the week.
Oh, my God, and we
should have been there
three fucking hours ago,
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
so let's go, bitches!
Holy shit. What?
Nothing.
You're just really gay.
Oh, am I?
Thanks, Captain Gaydar.
Jesus! You know,
I'm also black, right?
Yeah, I know.
That's funny, too.
So you guys wanna tag
along for a bit maybe?
Party some babies into us?
Absolutely not! Absolutely not!
Why? We have
a very important tee time.
Of course you do.
And do you also have to take a
nap before you play Mahjong?
No, it's shuffleboard.
Shuffleboard.
And then early dinner at 4:00.
DICK: We have a long-standing
bet. Who's the better golfer.
Obviously I've got
the bigger 3-wood...
Good. Maybe you can use it
to hit your balls
right into my vagina.
Holy shit! Okay, we're
going inside now.
Jesus! Let's go. That's enough.
Bye, Professor.
Thanks for lunch.
Peace!
Nice girl. Yeah.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
Well? How do I look?
Like the keynote speaker at
a buttfucking convention.
What? What?
We're gonna write
in the first hole,
it's an easy par-4.
No, no, no, no. Hey... Jump in.
This is against
the rules, Grandpa.
Fuck the rules.
Jump in. Come on.
Not to mention,
a breach in golf etiquette.
DICK: Beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep!
MAN: Whoa! Hey!
Out of my way, buttfuckers!
Really? What are you doing?
DICK: We gotta get this guy
to his buttfucking convention.
MAN: What are you
trying to do, man?
What was that all about?
Hey. Now there's
a million-dollar swing!
(CHUCKLING) I'm sorry! Um...
You can go in front of us
if you want to.
We are not very good.
No, it's a good cut,
you're just not bending
your knees enough.
I'm a licensed golf pro.
You mind if I show you?
Yes, please.
Maybe bend over
a little bit... Here.
That feels about right,
doesn't it?
Hands on my shaft... The shaft.
Let me just get
my finger in there.
One, two, three...
Oh!
Oh, my God! Did you see that?
Oh. Yeah.
Thank you!
How long have you
been teaching golf?
Ever since I retired
from being an astronaut.
It's nice to see some heavenly
bodies around here too.
Hey, Grandpa,
don't you think we should
probably start golfing soon...
What the fuck?
Wanna be a lamb
and get that for me?
Did he just call you "Grandpa"?
Who, Pepe? He's a retard.
Got it pretty bad, too.
He thinks I'm his grandpa.
He usually sits at home just
drawing dolphins all day.
We used to let him
out on his own,
but the raping got so bad
that we just...
Got it.
You guys want a refill?
WOMAN: Sure.
Absolutely! BRB!
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry about my grandpa.
He's, um...
He's not doing too well.
My grandma just passed and
the funeral was yesterday.
WOMEN: Oh...
I'm actually a lawyer,
not a retard.
I handle of lot
of important issues.
SEC compliance,
LLC agreements. LP agreements.
That sort of stuff.
Yeah, um, well, I think
we're gonna get going.
Nice to meet you, Pepe. Nice...
Fuck!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What happened?
Why are they going?
What did you do?
What? I told them the truth.
I told them that I'm getting
married next week,
and you're not well
because your wife just died.
What are you,
fucking vagina repellent?
Those cougars wanted to party!
They wanted to party? Yes!
Do you hear yourself?
Grandpa, are you kidding
me right now? Grandma...
I'm trying to listen to myself.
Grandma's funeral
was yesterday!
Now you wanna
hit on college girls?
(STAMMERS)
You're jerking off to porn?
What's wrong with you?
Jason, I want to fuck!
Oh, my God...
For the first time in 40 years
I'm single and I want to fuck.
(GROANS) I want to fuck
until my dick falls off.
I want to fuck a horse
and I wanna drink its blood!
I'm gonna throw up.
I was faithful
to your grandmother
every day for 40 years,
even through the menopause,
even through the cancer.
She was the love of my life.
I'll miss her
every goddamn day.
But she told me
on her deathbed,
"You get back out there again."
I haven't had sex
in 15 years, Jason,
and I want to fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh, so that's what
this is all about?
This whole thing. You
didn't want to be with me.
You wanted me
to drive you down to Boca
so I could be your
fucking wingman?
Well, obviously
I made a bad decision
because you're nothing but
a cock-blocking machine.
I don't know what you are.
You're like the Israeli
Iron Dome defense system,
but with vaginas
instead of missiles.
What? You're like some sort of
cock-blocking Terminator
sent back from the future
to cock-block humans.
Oh!
The robots should have sent you
instead of
Arnold Schwarzenegger,
you could have cock-blocked
John Connor's parents
and he would never
have been born!
Shut up, Grandpa!
Shut up! What got into you?
I remember you in high school,
you were ripping
people's dicks off
on the football field,
talking about
traveling the world!
Now you're pushing some
papers at a fucking law firm
and probably
peeing sitting down.
Grandpa, I don't know
what you thought
this weekend
was going to be about,
but I came here for one reason,
to get you to Boca.
That's it.
Fine.
Now can I please
play some golf?
Fucking golf. Okay.
Cocky McBlockerson.
What the fuck?
Bam!
Who does your taxes?
H&R Cock-block?
Stop it.
Bam!
Are you still Jenny
from the cock-block?
What the fuck! What is your
obsession with my ass?
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
Your vibrator's on.
You can't get into it anyway
because you don't know my code.
Looks like your grandpa
remembered your birthday!
What? Give me that!
We're going to fucking Daytona.
We're not going to Daytona,
because I've got
the keys to the golf cart.
What are you doing?
Hey. (ENGINE STARTING)
How'd you do that?
Coming or staying,
Jack Dicklaus?
Grandpa?
Hurry up, Bubba Twatson.
Grandpa, stop.
Gary Player-with-my-balls.
Stop the cart!
Fred Couples-of-big-dicks-
in-your-ass.
Oh, my God. Grandpa! Stop!
Michelle Wies-all-over-my-face.
(LATIN POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(PEOPLE WHOOPING)
DICK: Now, this is what
I'm fucking talking about.
This is so fucked up.
Calm down,
you'll get to hang out
with that gypsy girl you like.
I don't like her.
Oh, yes, you do.
That's why you didn't deny
being a photographer
for Time magazine.
You can hang out with her,
I can have
vaginal sex with Lenore.
It all works out!
We can even go visit
my old army buddy, Stinky.
Stinky? (SIGHS)
Which tiki bar are they in?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh, shit. Shit. Shit.
What's that? It's Meredith.
Please,
I've got to answer that.
Ah, tell her to fuck off.
Grandpa!
I'm just gonna check the testosterone
levels on your phone first.
Grandpa, give me my phone now!
Just as I thought. Pretty low.
This is Meredith calling...
Shit!
Now, look what you did,
you dropped it
in the car's vagina.
God damn it,
I have to put it on speaker.
Don't say anything.
I will not say a word.
(EXHALES)
Ballbags!
Hey! Who was that?
No one. We're in a restaurant.
Sorry.
(MIMICKING) "Who's that?"
What's up? Okay...
Well, I really want them
to post
our wedding announcement
on the New York Times website
before our rehearsal
brunch Friday,
so I just wanted to run
your section back to you.
Yeah, you know, now's
really not a good time...
Jason? Can we just
do this please?
(MIMICKING)
"Can we do this now?"
"Jason Richard Kelly,
son of..."
"Doctor Smegma
Von BoxMunchers."
"David and Brooke,"
"is a junior associate
at the law firm of..."
"Cream pie fart
and donkey punch!"
Okay, who is that?
It's no one. It's a waiter
with pretty bad Tourette's,
I think...
(HIP-HOP MUSIC BLARING)
He just keeps walking by
yelling weird shit,
I don't know why...
MEREDITH: Okay, well,
what restaurant are you at?
I can barely even hear you now.
We're at Chuck E. Cheese's...
(GRUNTING)
Daytona fucking Beach!
You're right, buddy!
You're in Daytona Beach?
Uh...
Listen, we're just driving
through Daytona Beach.
We're en route to Grandpa's...
Jason!
I don't know why you're there,
but you'd better call me
from your grandfather's house
when you get there
tonight, okay?
Of course, baby. I love you so much...
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
Fuck! Marriage is hard.
What'd the hot
college girls text back?
(CELL PHONE CHIMES) Grandpa,
what are you texting them?
I just texted them. What are you texting
them? "We'll meet you on the beach."
Yeah, and I added the emoji with
the wink and the tongue out.
JASON: I'm not kidding,
Grandpa.
You realize
that if I don't call her
from your house
in Boca tonight,
I'm fucked, man, I'm fucked.
Jesus. Sounds like
you're marrying
your fucking parole officer.
It's just Meredith.
It's the way she is, man.
She just gets, like, anxious
when she doesn't know
exactly where I am.
Don't panic. It's organic.
Yeah, I know. Couples get
in fights all the time.
But it's different
with Meredith.
She takes it
to another level, man,
and I'm telling you,
if I don't call her
from your house in Boca,
I'm screwed.
Well, ain't nobody
got time for that.
Yeah, I know. Clearly.
Which is why I don't understand
how we got so far off schedule.
Oh... Sometimes
life is just a fart zone,
and you enter at your own risk.
Have you been reading shit
off the shot glasses
and the shirts in here
and just saying it
like it's wisdom?
I was seriously trying
to talk to you, man.
Do you realize the stakes here?
You're ridiculous! Smile.
You've had a phone
this entire fucking time?
What else
don't I know about you?
How the hell do you know
how to speak Arabic?
Dad's never said
anything about that.
That's because your dad
doesn't really know
much about me.
I was away with the army
during most of his childhood.
So we were never that close.
Is that why
he doesn't like you?
Anybody work here?
Okay, everybody
on the fucking floor!
This is a goddamn robbery!
On the fucking ground!
(LAUGHING)
Oh, my God,
you should see your faces!
I just left to grab lunch
and a new horse mask.
I left mine at the beach
the other day. Whoo!
I thought you were gonna
shit your pants, little guy.
Gun's real though.
What the fuck, man!
Relax, this is Florida.
Everything's
a licensed gun range.
You just shot
through a wall, man!
Hey...
There's pedestrians outside!
Yeah, again, it's Florida!
These people don't matter.
What? So?
Welcome to Tam Pam Surf Slam.
What can I do for you
gentlemen? I'm Pam.
You're Pam?
Yeah. It's a nickname.
Real name's Pamela.
Hey, no, guys! Absolutely not!
I will not ever sell you drugs
out of this establishment!
We didn't ask you
to sell us drugs.
Okay, cool. You're not cops.
In which case,
welcome to drugs!
Oh, my God.
Now, I'm pretty cool,
so I only sell the stuff
that occurs naturally.
So I got weed, I got
mushrooms, I got meth.
Meth? Yeah.
How is that natural?
Well, it occurs naturally in my
cousin's basement in Baltimore,
if you know what I mean.
(LAUGHS)
Okay, fine.
Drugs aren't your thing,
got it.
Message received.
In which case,
listen, we got a great
local charity here.
Pam's Kidz.
What's Pam's Kidz?
That's my kids.
I got four kids by
six different women.
I know, the numbers
don't add up.
Most of them are pretty
developmentally disabled.
One of them you gotta push
around in a wheelchair.
(COIN CLINKING) PAM: Hey-o!
Now that is the generosity
of the human spirit
and I appreciate that.
Now some of this money
is gonna feed my kids,
some of it is gonna
get me a blowjob
by a toothless whore behind the
dumpster down at the McDonalds.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey. Hey.
Hi, Professor.
Well, there's the prettiest
little girl on the beach.
Thank you.
I was actually talking to him.
Yup! Immediately offensive.
I'm going back to the hotel.
Just try not to join the cast
of Rent on the way back!
(BRADLEY GROANS)
So we got the Professor,
you got the millionaire.
How's the rest
of the Gilligan's Island cast?
We're good.
Yeah? Yeah, everyone's good.
Well, that's good.
Copacetic on the island.
(LAUGHS)
How are those washed-out
pictures you're taking
because you still have
the lighting optimizer on?
They're not... Where is that?
Actually, it's really
hypersensitive
on the new 60D model.
So you have to...
Wait. What is that?
SHADIA: Okay, nope.
What are you doing?
Give it back, Malibu Ken.
No... What?
You did it. You turned
into one of those people.
I turned into
one of those people
that gives a shit
about something?
Are you gonna chain
yourself to a polar bear?
Only if you let me borrow...
What is this, a beach sweater?
Yeah. What, did you
just come from skiing?
Yeah, I skied in,
just to see you save the world.
One Jell-O shot at a time.
High-five!
You want me to do your back?
Only if you promise
to do my front first.
Gladly.
Oh. Whoops!
That never usually happens.
Really? It happens to me
all the time.
(LAUGHING) Well, guess who just
took a shit in the water? Ow!
CODY: We've been looking
for you bitches all day.
Where the fuck have you been?
Uh, our car broke down
in Orlando.
Do you ever
look at your cell phone?
Awesome.
Who are these cunt punches?
These are
our friends that we met
on the way down. Yeah.
That's Cody and Brah.
They're on the
lacrosse team at Florida.
This guy plays lacrosse?
All-conference, brah!
Yeah? Which one, the fucking
Diabetes Conference?
(LAUGHING)
All right, we're about to boat
race a bunch of those fucks
from the University of Georgia
up in the room. So...
Oh, my God!
University of Georgia!
No way! You're a Hornet?
Afraid so.
Well, you guys
should get in there then,
Edward Jizzumhands.
Well, thank you. We will.
Good, that's great.
I'll see you up there.
Oh, good. Well,
you say we'll be there
and on time.
Sweet. I will. Yeah.
Yeah, let's do that.
No, we should. Let's do it now.
Yeah, I'll see you up there.
What...
Come to the hotel. By the pool.
Georgia sucks!
Can we please just go?
They've got boyfriends.
Those meatdick fucks? They're
not their boyfriends.
They're just seniors,
and they're all just terrified
and speed-fucking each other
before the ship goes down.
Didn't you ever
go on Spring Break?
No, I didn't go
to Spring Break,
'cause I was studying
for law school.
Besides, I can't
chug alcohol anymore
like I used to, Grandpa.
I've developed,
like, a gag reflex.
A gag reflex? Yeah.
You're chugging a beer,
not taking down
a horse cock, Jason.
Come on.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Go Hornets!
Go Hornets, yeah...
Hey, you know, one in three
of these girls has herpes.
Even if you can't see it.
Oh, Jesus. Nut the fuck up.
It's just a college party,
you nance. Chill!
Hey, here they are.
I'm gonna get some beers.
What about you, twinkle toes?
You want some of dat drank?
Some of dat purple drank?
Some of dat
purple-ass muthafuckin'
pimp-dick drank?
Who the fuck are you?
It's a pretty rockin' party.
Whoo.
Who let the dogs out?
Am I right?
Sir, before we start,
would you prefer
if we gave you
a spritzer to chug?
Ah... Maybe a Pinot Noir?
You're going down, old man.
Nobody chugs like me.
I bet. You've been chugging
Brah's cum for years.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Let's go.
(TRIUMPHANT CLASSICAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
CROWD: (CHANTING) Chug!
Chug!
Go! Go! Chug!
(INAUDIBLE)
It's actually kind of fun.
(ALARM BLARING)
Yeah, I'm not really,
you know, for sure,
per say... (GROANING)
what we're doing
after graduation.
I mean,
we have offers to play...
Blah, blah, blah...
professional
lacrosse in Europe,
but a bunch of agents...
Words, words, words...
also want us to
start modeling, so...
And again, we're talking about
this fat fuck right here?
SHADIA: You guys...
Uh, you have
to come see this right now.
(LATIN POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
All right, our team won!
Let's celebrate
by buying local drugs
from a reputable,
local drug dealer.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm selling drugs, man.
I'm trying to put my kid
through preschool.
(LAUGHING)
How honest is that!
Touching my face a lot, bro.
Touching my face
a whole lot, man.
Why don't you take some of this.
This'll mellow you out.
What is it? E-cig, bro.
"E" is for "Weed"!
(LAUGHS)
Sure, why not?
(INHALING)
Yeah, ooh, that's a big...
That's a big one.
Oh!
(COUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Whoo!
Just be glad you didn't smoke this, man.
This is crack!
What? Oh, yeah!
This one...
Oh, wait a minute...
Maybe that one's crack
and this one's weed.
Hang on.
What'd you do now, Pam?
Fuck. Hold on.
Which one's crack?
Okay. I got this.
Don't freak out.
Sorry to worry you, man.
You're not gonna believe this.
They're both crack.
What?
And you have taken an amount
that will probably kill you
in about 30 minutes.
I just smoked crack? Yeah.
But just, like, a lot.
I just smoked crack.
I just smoked crack!
(ALL CHEERING)
ALL: (CHANTING) USA!
USA!
Told you.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
He's fine.
He's just a little drunk.
(ALL CHEERING)
Whoo!
Everybody loves crack!
Bee loves crack.
Bee loves some crack.
We should probably go help him.
(MIMICKING BUZZING)
Sting? You're stung!
(CAMERA CLICKS)
Oh, shit,
I just found my queen.
All right. (GRUNTS)
Okay, let's help him.
(MIMICKING GORILLA)
SHADIA: Excuse me. Jason!
(WHOOPING) (CROWD CHEERING)
Hey, Jason. SHADIA: Jason.
(GRUNTING)
Jason. Jason.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
(MOTORCYCLE ENGINE STARTS)
I'm gonna live forever!
WOMAN: Party on!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GASPS)
Oh, shit!
(PANTING)
One, two, three...
Hello? Where the
fuck have you been?
Uh...
We got to Grandpa's a little bit
later than we thought last night,
and my phone charger
wasn't working.
Well, you know
we missed the deadline
for our wedding announcement
to be in the Times.
Where are you? Are you close?
Um...
Listen, Grandpa got
really upset last night.
So I'm just getting
a little bit of
a late jump here.
I want to show you the
bouquets for the bridesmaids.
So switch to FaceTime, okay?
Shit! Baby, the reception at
Grandpa's isn't very good...
Jason, just fucking do it!
Okay, one second.
Switching over.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Is that sand on your face?
(STAMMERS) It's just sawdust
because I was helping
Grandpa in the garage, so...
I naturally got the dust
of the saw on the face.
Hi, honey. Jason.
Mom? Dad?
Is that writing on your face?
Oh! I was working on my vows
late last night and...
Hmm...
And I fell asleep and I got
some pen on my face, so...
Yeah, that must be
the exact thing that happened.
DAVID: Yeah, Meredith
called us because
she hadn't
heard from you all night.
We got the rabbi here
to work on the vows.
Boker tov, Jason.
Hey. Shalom.
No, Jason, really...
What is on your forehead?
It's a swastika of penises.
No, that's not what it is.
Acting as a pinwheel
of ejaculate...
No, no, no,
it's a FaceTime effect.
All the kids are using
them these days.
There's a Hanukkah one. See?
I don't like that one as much
as the swastika full of dicks.
RABBI: Okay, let's discuss
the wedding vows.
Jason, why don't you
begin by telling us all
what it is you like
about Meredith.
(STAMMERS) Yeah, where do I start?
She's...
Hello.
Uh...
Hello, buzzy bee.
What?
If you can't think of anything,
lean into them looks, dawg.
Can I touch buzzy bee?
I've loved her for... (WHISPERS)
No, you can't touch buzzy bee!
Um...
I love the way that she, um...
What are you doing? Stop it!
Go away! You're getting me in...
Fuck, go away!
BOY: Your buzzy bee
looks so fluffy!
What did he say?
I just don't know
where to start.
BOY: Let me touch buzzy bee!
You can't have the bee!
What?
I want to stroke the bee!
JASON: You can't
stroke the bee! Okay?
BOY: I want to kiss buzzy bee!
JASON: You can't kiss the bee!
I love the way that she kisses.
Ow! Kid! MAN: Hey!
JASON: Oh, my God... MAN: Hey!
Fucking pervert! Oh, no.
I got to go right now.
I'm sorry.
I love you. Bye!
No, no, no! Jason! Jason!
Come on. I told you
to stay with us.
He let me stroke it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on! He's talking
about a pee... A bee.
A little stuffed bee.
What bee?
There was a bee here, man!
It was so soft.
He let me kiss it.
No, I did not let you kiss it!
What are you talking about?
He did not even... Ahhh!
You're fucking dead!
Dad, that was cool!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Oh, shit!
May I have some pants?
Please...
Oh, Jesus Christ, I'm so sorry.
Of course.
Yeah, absolutely.
You want khakis or sweatpants?
Khakis, please.
What brand? You like Docker's?
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah? Okay.
All right. You're like a 30...
Uh, yes, 30 is fine.
What I wouldn't give
to fit in a 30.
Maybe 20 years ago, you know.
When I was seven years old.
Yeah. All right.
Also, I'm going to step
out and get some lunch.
Do you want a sandwich?
I would love a sandwich.
Ham? Turkey?
Turkey? Turkey.
That's so funny, because I'm a
turkey guy myself, you know.
Thank you so much.
Okay. Absolutely want
mayo on that?
Uh, no, thank you, no. Okay.
Uh, extra veggies.
Extra veggies?
Yes, please.
You got it. Absolutely...
Salt and vinegar.
You want salt
and vinegar as well?
Yeah, thank you.
You gotta watch that sodium.
All right, because that's what
drives your blood pressure up.
And blood pressure
is a silent killer.
Turkey... Okay... All right...
Yeah. And, uh, finally,
do you want to be sodomized
by a man with the
mental age of seven
who calls himself "Ping-pong",
or do you want to be shivved
by the, uh, same guy?
Just let me know
what time works out for you,
'cause you're in fucking jail.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
All right. Gary, I'm all done.
It's late.
I gotta go open
the store, buddy.
I know, but you tried to sell
peyote to middle schoolers.
What? Come on, it's me. Pam.
Don't be a dick.
Come on! I just had watery diarrhea.
I wanna get out of here.
It stinks! It does stink.
All right,
let's get you out of there.
(LAUGHS) All right. Whoo!
I don't like being in a cage.
Wait, you're letting him out?
He's the one that sold drugs.
Why are you letting him out?
Hey, man! Not cool!
That's a real dick move
throwing me under the bus.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
You're the one
that sold drugs last night.
Hey, guy.
Snitches get stitches!
All right.
So why don't you shut
your fucking mouth, bro.
OFFICER REITER: Yeah. Snitches
get stitches, my friend.
(LAUGHS) My name's Pam.
OFFICER REITER:
You are just incorrigible.
Hey. How are you, Finch?
How you doing, hon?
Good to see you. Hey.
Finchy. Jean Finch.
You got it. Most beautiful woman
on the police force right here.
Jeez. The only woman...
(LAUGHTER)
Here's the deal. What's up?
I came in here with
a bag of drugs.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I can't leave without it.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Can you guys hook me up there?
Yeah.
Ooh! Gary! Yeah. These yours?
Thanks, Gar-bear.
Oh, nice catch.
PAM: Please remember
next Tuesday is the election.
Vote for me for mayor.
I'm gonna win this year.
I'm gonna beat that goat.
(LAUGHS)
Pam! Pam! FINCH: My God.
He is just a good one.
He is the number one...
Lover and a fighter...
Okay, listen.
Guys, I really respect
the job you guys do.
I'm being completely honest
from the bottom of my heart,
I look up to you.
I fight for the law.
Thank you. No one ever
says that to us. Ever.
That's what I wanted to do
when I was a kid.
I wanna do what you guys do.
Mostly people just call us pigs and
throw bags of fast food at us.
I'm incredibly sorry for all this
confusion, but listen to me,
please, I have to
let you know I'm a lawyer.
Whoa, whoa! You're a lawyer?
Wait a second.
Yeah, I'm actually a lawyer.
Whoa. You don't look
like a lawyer. No.
Yeah, I handle, like,
uh, corporate stuff.
Like, uh, like LLC agreements.
LP... You lost me. I don't
even know what that means.
I mean, you don't look Jewish.
No.
(SIGHS) If you think about it,
it's actually pretty funny.
(LAUGHING)
Like, ending up here
on this side...
It is. That is funny.
It is so weird.
It's darkly ironic.
It really is.
Yes, exactly. Dark irony.
I thought you had to be, like,
at least 80 to be a lawyer.
(SCOFFS) Lawyer. Like, it's
a lot of school, right?
Yeah.
(STAMMERS)
It's a lot of school.
The bar...
It's something I took
and passed.
It's not something
I stand behind.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
I'm not on this side,
typically,
and I just, uh... I just...
I know my rights and
I would love my phone call.
Objection. Overruled.
Permission to approach the bench.
Denied!
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) What?
It's easy to be a lawyer.
It's so easy.
(STAMMERING)
I would love my phone call.
(BOTH MOCKING)
Okay?
I know my rights.
I want my phone call.
(BOTH CONTINUE MOCKING)
Give me my phone call.
I should have a phone...
This is my
First Amendment right.
It is my first... First and foremost...
Page one, number one...
amendment says that
I get my telephone.
And most of all,
can I get a phone call?
This is my
First Amendment right.
(MOCKINGLY) I don't think you understand
that I'm guaranteed a phone call.
I don't sound like that.
(MOCKINGLY) Yeah?
What do you sound like then?
Um, not like that. I don't
think I sound like that.
(BOTH CONTINUE MOCKING)
Give me my phone call.
Oh, please, will you let me have
my phone call? ...phone call.
I'm an American and
I'm fucking guaranteed...
I'm an American.
I am guaranteed a phone call.
(MOCKINGLY) Legally, it's my
right to have a phone call.
I just said I'm an American
and I'm guaranteed
a phone call.
Hmm. Well, now
he's getting demanding.
Yeah. We better give
him his phone call.
(MOCKINGLY) Better
give him his phone call.
Guys, come on. Come on, please.
It doesn't...
Why are we doing this?
This is your phone
right here, right?
That is my phone. Yes.
Well, you know what?
We get to make one phone
call on your phone.
That's where you're just
a little bit mixed up.
Yeah. Hopefully, you're not
out of "framily" minutes.
No, no, no, no, no... Yeah, we
get a free Uber ride on that.
Go ahead. Take us out to lunch.
Hey, you know what? We're gonna
be kind and set you up with
a Tinder account too.
OFFICER REITER: Ooh, how about Grindr.
What about...
OFFICER FINCH: Look at
this, look at this.
"Jefe", is that how
you pronounce that?
Yeah, how about Jefe?
Yeah. Huh? Little
alone time with Jefe?
He'd like some light conversation
and heavy petting, flirting...
Flirtations.
OFFICER REITER: Hmm.
He looks thick and lonely.
OFFICER FINCH: You'll meet him at 8:00.
You'll bring wine coolers.
And...
Children's condoms. (LAUGHS)
Just gonna take a little picture.
Oh.
Snatch-chat.
Yeah, a little snach-chat.
Please don't do that
with my phone.
Hope you got a wide
angle lens on that.
Oh! Wow. (PHONE RINGING)
(CHUCKLES)
Kidding.
Somebody just posted his bail.
Get that pervert some pants.
OFFICER FINCH: All right.
These were a couple
pair of pants
from murder victims from
a 1990s orgy gone bad.
We got semen-stained
or blood-stained.
Take your pick.
What's it gonna be?
Blood. Semen it is.
Hey, there he is. No.
Don't even fucking talk to me.
Oh. Look, I know things
got a little chaotic,
but I'm so close with Lenore...
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
I'm about to get fucking
married, Grandpa!
In one week! To a Jewish girl!
And I just woke up
in fucking jail
with a bunch of penises
on my forehead
in the shape of a swastika!
Could call it a swasticock.
What? It's a play on words.
Oh, it's a play on words.
A play on words.
Play on these words.
I'm dropping you off
at your old army vet
buddy's house,
he's gonna drive you
to fucking Boca.
Because I'm fucking
done with you.
What the fuck
are you looking at?
I can't help
staring at your tits.
Pow!
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
You know, Stinky
had more confirmed kills
than anyone in our platoon
back in 'Nam? 118.
Shut the fuck up.
What is this place?
I don't know. Or care.
At least just come in with me.
Let's make sure
it's the right house.
After you.
Grandson of the year.
Your grandmother's
ashes are in there.
She's in a coffin. Fuck you!
Oh, well,
better late than never.
Yeah! Fuck them up, ALF!
Motherfucker!
Stinky?
What the fuck are you
doing here, Dick?
Oh, this?
Nah, this is liver failure.
Who's the lesbian?
That's my grandson, Jason.
Yeah?
Is he here to scissor with me?
Okay, that's just
offensive to lesbians.
I am very sorry, k.d. lang.
Time for Bingo!
Come on. Stinky, we got to get
you the fuck out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Uh, I got one fucking
month left, Dick!
I don't want you to
remember me like this, man.
I want you to remember
me as a warrior.
Please. Leave me be.
But, Stinky...
No, no, no...
Just let me finish, Dick.
Leave me your beautiful
lesbian grandson
so he can blowjob me to death.
It's all over for me, Dick.
You know, all I wanna
do is play Bingo.
Go.
NURSE: All ready?
Bingo! (LAUGHING)
I'm sorry about
your friend, Grandpa.
So it comes to this.
Even before you die,
you just stop living,
and it's all one fucked-up
facsimile of the real thing.
We have to go back.
(SIGHS)
Yeah. I know.
I'll drive us home.
Not Atlanta. Daytona.
What?
I have to fuck
that girl, Jason.
Jesus, Grandpa! I do.
I have to fuck her!
Grandpa, you're just depressed.
You're confused right now
because of Grandma.
Grandma wanted me to do this.
What? Yeah. She
said when she died,
she wanted me to move on
and live my life
the way I wanted to,
and right now, you know
what I want to do?
I want to get my dick sucked
by that fucking college girl!
What is that
going to do for you?
Is that going to make
you feel young again?
Yeah! Yeah, what's
wrong with that?
Yeah?
Feeling young again?
What do I have?
A dead wife, dying friends.
A few fucking good
years left if I'm lucky.
And you know what?
It fucking freaks me out!
Yeah.
Look, I don't expect
you to understand.
You're young.
You have a long, long time
before you have to
look into that abyss.
But the way I see it,
having sex with that girl
is my last stand.
And I can't do it without you.
So I'm asking you.
Please, Jason,
just stay one more day
so I can do this.
Please.
(SIGHS)
Okay, Daytona Beach!
Who's ready for a Flex Off!
I'm talking about dudes
getting on stage,
getting ripped!
Yeah!
Yes, I'll be home
tomorrow. I promise.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
And I know... Yes,
I know the dinner
is important to the firm...
Hold on,
I'm getting another call.
It might be Meredith.
Okay? Bye.
Hello? DICK: Hey, it's me.
Someone just stuck
their thumb up my ass.
What?
Yeah, I was just
standing right there,
talking on the phone,
and someone came
right up behind me
and stuck their thumb
up my ass.
Did you see who it was...
Jamba!
Ow! Fuck! Stop doing that!
How'd it go on the home front?
How do you think?
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Top Gun in the house!
We got Maverick!
We got Fat Goose!
Do we have a challenger?
Right here! Right here!
These two! She wants to!
These two.
Pick her!
Who will accept
this challenge?
You go up there,
I'll let you do
whatever you want
to me tonight.
All right, I'm doing it. Okay!
What? Whoo!
No, no, no! Are you kidding me?
I saw your body last night,
it's a lot better than Cody's.
And my body sure
as shit looks better
than that fucking
Shamu's up there.
There's, like, 1,000
people out here!
PAM: A lost old man
has wandered on stage.
Are you his nurse?
No. Fuck no.
Get on stage! Get on stage!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Do it for me!
Get on stage! Get on stage!
(ALL CHEERING)
So we have team Top Gun
versus creepy old guy
and his lesbian daughter.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Okay, Daytona Beach,
are you ready to Flex Off?
Three! Two! One!
Flex!
Ooh, having trouble getting
that coat off, Fat Goose?
Uh...
PAM: Look at this guy!
He's like
Mother Teresa's vagina!
Old and tight!
Hey, look,
it's Cirque du So Gay!
(LAUGHS)
What now?
PAM: Uh-oh!
Has the old man fallen?
Uh... Or is it...
One-armed
motherfucking push-ups!
Holy shit!
Lesbian daughter's
getting in on the action!
I happen to know he
smoked crack last night!
These push-ups are fuelled
by the devil's candy!
Unbelievable! (ALL CHEERING)
Your move, Dolly Parton.
PAM: What are you gonna
do now, team Top Gun?
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
And, hey, everybody,
don't forget to stop by.
Tam Pam Surf Slam in town
where I'm selling
"beach towels"
for 50 bucks an ounce.
"Sun screen"
for 10 bucks a dime bag.
And I'm also selling meth!
(ALL CHEERING) Oh!
Just got married!
Your move, Viagra Falls.
Crowd going wild
for team Top Gun!
Grandpa, I got this. Watch!
Most muscular, on three.
One, two, three.
(FARTING OVER SPEAKERS)
Oh! I think this guy
just sharted!
No, I didn't! Yes!
Call a lifeguard, I think
there's been a shart attack!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PAM MIMICS HIGH-PITCHED FART)
I'm not even holding
the mic right now.
(ALL LAUGHING)
WOMAN: You suck!
I have an idea.
Do you remember that thing we
used to do when I was a kid?
Yeah.
One, two, three...
Hold on, what's this?
What is going on?
Oh, my God, what am I seeing?
(ALL CHEERING)
Am I on drugs? Of course I am!
But this is still incredible!
Flex Off history
is being made!
What's up now, Brah?
Yeah, what's up now, Brah?
PAM: Yeah, 'sup now, Brah?
'Sup now, Brah?
ALL: (CHANTING) 'Sup now, Brah?
This is incredible!
Take out your cameras!
Put this online!
This shit is going viral!
Shit. Let me down.
Did everybody
get a picture of that?
What the fuck are you doing?
I can't do this... What?
God... The winners
of the Alpha Delta Flex Off...
Wait a minute!
Where are you going? Wh...
Guys? Hey! Where are you going?
Jason!
PAM: You can't just
leave me here like this.
Why'd you stop?
We were winning!
JASON: Because I'm a lawyer!
I can't have people taking pictures
of me doing stuff like this.
Can you imagine if the firm
saw something like that?
PAM: By default, the winner
of the Flex Off is...
Bring the cup home, baby!
These two dildos.
(CROWD BOOING)
Every single day,
my career's in jeopardy...
What are you doing?
I'm taking the regulator off
the pneumatic
propulsion system.
Give me a beer.
Grandpa, what did you
really do for the army?
I told you, I was a mechanic.
Bullshit.
You speak Arabic.
You hotwired a golf cart.
Tell me the truth.
All right,
I was Special Forces!
I trained insurgents behind enemy
lines from Vietnam to Iraq.
Now give me the fucking
beer can! Come on!
(BOTH CHEERING)
PAM: Look at this dummy!
What an idiot!
(GROANS)
Whoo!
Yeah! Do it again!
We can change in Cody's room.
I picked his pocket earlier.
PAM: All right. Nothing
to see here, guys.
Cops are gonna
come pretty quick.
No, no, this is his father,
so that's what I'm saying.
Keep him heavily sedated,
but don't be afraid to pull
the plug if you have to.
Thank you, Doctor.
Okay. They're in the
hospital till tomorrow!
The room's ours for the night.
Look at these fucking people.
How was brunch at
Hitler's house that day?
Hey, Grandpa, who else
in our family knows
that you were, uh, Special
Forces or whatever?
No one, once your
grandmother passed.
Your father stopped
talking to me
before my missions
were declassified.
So he always thought
I was just an army mechanic.
But don't you think
that you guys would
get along a little better
if you told him?
Hey, come on. Let's see
how you look. Come on out.
First of all,
nobody wears
a fucking white belt.
The only people
who wear white belts
are people who suck at karate
and people who suck at life.
Take the fucking belt off.
And you better lose that
fucking white polo shirt
and those pleated khaki pants.
You're meeting up with girls,
not blowing an oil executive
on a fucking golf course.
Put these on.
Well, in case you forgot,
I don't even have
underwear, from last night.
All right, just put them on.
I'll turn around.
Nice dick. Aw, jeez, Grandpa.
That's a good dick. You
got your grandpa's dick.
Not the girth, not the
length, but same style.
That's good to know.
You're lucky
you're not your dad.
He's got his mom's dick.
What the fuck? (LAUGHS)
Now put your pants on.
(1950s MUSIC PLAYING)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
Shit. It's Meredith.
Don't answer it.
My rehearsal brunch
is this weekend.
No calls. For one night,
stop worrying about your wedding.
Please.
We have two hot, smart,
beautiful college girls
at the peak of their
sexual powers
about to meet us at one of the
last great nightclubs in Florida.
Worry about them.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
(WOMEN CHEERING)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't think you're very
popular here, Grandpa.
Hey. You're the one that's
going to have to watch out.
You might get Oreo'd.
Oreo'd?
That's when two black guys
fuck a white guy.
You're the cream in the middle.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
DICK: Game on.
Hey! Glad you guys made it.
Let's go get fucked up. Right?
My stepdad hates me!
(CHUCKLES)
Let's go!
Party till you're pregnant!
(ALL WHOOPING)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING) Oh,
my God, I love this song!
You're not gonna
die on me, are you?
I don't think so. All right!
Come on. Oh, no. No.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, yeah. You want it? Come
here, give me that hat!
BRADLEY: Oh, my God...
(BRADLEY WHIMPERS)
Give me that! What is this?
Hey! Hey, hey, hey...
Leave my illegitimate
black son alone.
We were just
asking him to dance.
Well, he don't wanna dance.
Well, maybe you
wanna dance instead.
I don't wanna dance...
Colonel Sanders!
It's all right. It's all right.
Let's not dirty this place up.
It's a shrine. Sinatra sang here.
Parking lot?
It'll be fine.
How is this going to be fine?
Look at this crew.
Come on. We have
a good crew too.
We have no crew.
Are we going to J.Crew?
Fuck J.Crew.
Don't do this.
I think I'm going to
have to fight them all,
so you're going to have
to take the first punch.
What? Okay! He's up first.
Whatever. (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
You like that shit, white boy?
Dude, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
What? You want next, bitch?
(BODIES THUDDING)
Hey, I thought I had next.
(ALL GROANING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Tell him you're sorry you made
fun of him for being gay.
(BONES CRACKING) (GROANS)
I'm sorry I made fun
of you for being gay!
Tell him you were raised
in a different era,
but now you know it's
wrong to judge people
based on their
sexual orientation.
And that if you had to
be gay with someone
for some reason,
you know, to prevent a
terrorist attack or something,
it would be with him.
What? Ow!
Say it.
(STRAINING) If I had to
be gay with somebody
to prevent a terrorist attack,
it would be you!
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Apology accepted.
Okay.
Get out of here
before I use my other arm.
(PANTING)
This ain't over.
Ooh! Oh!
Now fuck off and
take Jodeci with you.
Let's roll.
Ah, it's too bad Lenore barfed
all over herself tonight.
I definitely could have
had sex with her.
Yup.
I probably could have
still had sex
if she just threw up
on her front,
but she somehow got
it all over her back,
and I would have felt bad.
Well, chivalry isn't dead.
I like the way you took
that haymaker tonight.
Sometimes you just gotta take
that punch up front, you know?
Then things get easier
in the long run.
"De Oppresso Liber."
It's written on your knife too.
What does that mean?
Hey, lights out
after 12:00, boys.
I better not catch you swimming
across the lake
to the girls' camp, okay?
Night. Good night.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You know, maybe I'll
find something to do
with Shadia tomorrow
and give you and Lenore
a little more alone time.
(SIGHS)
I kind of feel like we're
just getting in your way.
Yeah?
I'm sure there's something...
What the fuck?
Did you just get naked?
Well, it's the best
way to sleep.
Oh, my God!
I picked it up in Uganda
from the Umbatdo.
Umbat-don't let your junk
touch my leg again
or you're sleeping
on the floor.
Night.
DICK: (WHISPERING) Jason...
The fuck! Oh, my God!
(CAMERA CLICKS)
What do these guys want to cut
all the trees down for anyway?
For some stupid, like,
massive, tacky
entertainment complex.
You know, the ones with,
like, arcades
and laser tag.
That sort of thing.
Laser tag? I love laser tag.
Yeah.
When does it open?
Nice. Thanks a lot.
Shadia! Hi, Griz.
Oh, my God, your pics from
the Boston rally look amazing!
Thank you. Yeah. Absolutely.
Sweet Hacky Sack, man.
It's not a Hacky Sack, dawg.
That's the trade name.
It's an organic
hemp-seed foot satchel.
And what's someone from the fucking
laser tag lobby doing here?
No, I'm just
a friend of Shadia's.
Just a friend.
That's pretty cool, man.
What is that, a dance ball?
Fuck! What the fuck?
(ALL LAUGHING)
You're fucking kidding me.
(MOCKINGLY) Dancing ball...
(MIMICS GUNS FIRING)
What the fuck!
It's a 4-inch acrylic
juggling orb!
Dick.
Um... I'll see you guys,
uh, next weekend.
GRIZ: Absolutely. Absolutely.
Yeah? Okay. Bye.
WOMAN: Love your necklace.
Bye.
Hey, Griz...
Don't touch that,
it's from Laser Tag.
Sorry.
They're good people. I swear.
Let me see that.
Where are you going
with these "good people"?
We're heading out to the coast
to, um, charter
a boat for the year.
For the year? Yeah.
(CHUCKLES) To do what?
We're documenting the effects
of climate change
out on the ocean.
Aren't you supposed
to graduate next weekend?
Yeah.
(CLICKS) (LAUGHS)
Seems to me like you're
running from something.
Come on, haven't you
had to make sacrifices
to get where you are
as a photographer?
I mean, yeah, but...
That's different.
Look at this.
I hate photos of myself.
Why?
You look beautiful.
See?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey.
Wait, just calm down.
What?
Shit. Yeah,
we'll be right there.
What's going on? We gotta go.
And then I came back
from the bathroom
and all those black
guys from the club
were, like, standing around
Lenore and Dr. Richards
and they were yelling at
them and threatening them
and they, like, kidnapped them!
And I think one
of them had a gun!
Did you see
where they took them?
No. (CELL PHONE BUZZING)
Those guys are staying
at The Tillman.
And that's all I know.
Okay. Come on!
Come on! Shit!
What?
(SNIFFING)
(WHISPERING) I smell marijuana.
BRADLEY: Mmm-hmm.
What are you going to
do with a bucket?
I don't know!
Okay, on three. Ready?
One, two, three!
Okay, let me try one more time.
The GZA, the RZA,
Ol' Dirty Bastard.
What's going on?
Gang stuff.
Raekwon the Chef!
(ALL CHEERING)
And the Method Man!
Hey! Here they are!
How was the protest?
Uh, it was good.
Yeah, it was good.
This is Lamar,
Lil' Chris, Big Chris,
Murray Finkelstein.
And, of course, you've
already met Ty-rizone.
(CHUCKLES)
That nigga's crazy, man.
Yeah, what's with
the N-word, anyway?
I can say it. I can't say it...
You can say it
when we let you say it.
Which is never.
Just never say that
under any circumstances.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
MAN: Oh! Shotgun!
(LAUGHS)
What the fuck is going on?
I thought these guys
wanted to kill you!
Lebanese Red.
I had some of this left over
from my time
in the Middle East.
You throw some of
this shit around,
you can really
get away with anything.
Have some.
You're smoking grass now?
Jesus, this is a
gateway drug, Grandpa.
Yeah, well, you just opened
the gateway to being a pussy.
Take some. Yo, D.
Let's fucking bounce!
JASON: Where?
(RAPPING) ♪ And
everything is all right
♪ I got a beep from Kim
And she can fuck all night
♪ Called up the homies
and I'm asking y'all
♪ Which park are y'all
playing basketball?
♪ Get me on the court
and I'm trouble
♪ Last week fucked around
And got a triple double.
Can I say it? Can I say it?
No! No, no.
Say it! Say that shit!
♪ Freaking niggas
every way like MJ
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
♪ I can't believe
today was a good day ♪
I'm totally gonna
fuck him tonight.
Uh-huh. Can I watch?
'Cause I kind of want
to fuck him too now.
Drop the mic, baby!
That's what I'm talking about!
Peace out, niggas!
I see you, boy. (GRUNTS)
Nasty!
Up next we have
Shadia and Jason!
Yep, that's us now.
What? No. No, no, no, no.
No... Come on.
We can't top that.
I don't want to do this.
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
You know the song.
You know every word. See?
You're going to make me
do it all alone?
Fine.
Hey.
♪ For all those times
you stood by me
♪ For all the truth
that you made me see
♪ For all the joy
you brought to my life
♪ For all the wrong
that you made right
♪ For every dream
you made come true
♪ For all the love
I found in you
♪ I'll be forever
thankful, baby
♪ You're the one
who held me up
♪ And never let me fall
Yeah, yeah
♪ You're the one
who saw me through
♪ Through it all
♪ You were my strength
when I was weak
♪ You were my voice
when I couldn't speak
♪ You were my eyes
when I couldn't see
♪ You saw the best
there was in me
♪ Lifted me up
when I couldn't reach
♪ You gave me faith
'cause you believed
♪ I'm everything I am.
Damn!
♪ Because you loved me ♪
(EXHALES)
Who are you?
SHADIA: I'm just saying,
who sings that well
and isn't
a professional singer?
You're so good at singing
you actually suck!
You guys want to come up
for a nightcap?
Yeah, well...
See if shit gets real?
Well, uh, young
Michael Buble and I
are gonna have a stogie
by the pool, so...
Okay.
See you up there? Yeah.
I want you to know
how much I appreciate
you doing this for me, Jason.
The greatest gift a grandson
can give his grandfather
is a hot college girl who
wants to have unprotected sex
with him before he dies.
Yeah, well, most grandpas
just want toffee.
(SIGHS)
What's the matter?
I think I'm gonna
call off my wedding.
Well, when you get married,
it's for a long fucking time.
And it's hard.
So it damn well
better be with a woman
who keeps things interesting.
You know your grandmother,
she tried to grow
her own pot plant once?
Really? Yeah,
she just wanted to see
if she could do it.
(LAUGHS)
She was always
surprising me like that.
We also tried anal
once every five years.
Sweet.
I miss having someone
to share everything with.
It's not fair
to just keep Shadia
in the dark like this.
Since we started this,
it's just been one big lie.
She has no idea who I am.
I have to tell her the truth.
Uh, well, maybe telling her
tonight is a little abrupt.
The most important part
of a relationship is trust.
That's right.
And I'm going to start now.
Or you can just wait till I
have sex with Lenore tonight,
then you can tell
Shadia everything.
No. I'm just lying.
Jason, I'm your grandfather!
You wait till I fuck
that college girl!
I'm telling her now. Jason...
Jason! Jason!
Jason!
(LAUGHS)
'Sup, brah?
Back off, D cups!
Well, if it isn't
the "Professor."
You know, it's amazing
what you can find
with a name and
Google these days.
You're not a real professor?
Oh, my God! You lied to us.
How could you.
Wait, wait, wait,
this is the best part.
This is the best part.
Richard "Dick" Kelly,
Lieutenant Colonel
in the United States Army,
also known as the American
Gladiator "Nitro."
What the fuck did you Google?
Okay, well, there's
another best part then.
"Jason Patrick Kelly will wed
Meredith Miriam Goldstein"
"at Jericho Temple
on Saturday, March 27th."
Oh, wait, that's,
um, next Saturday.
Wait, you're grandfather
and grandson?
Oh, my God!
That is so fucked up.
That is so hot. I mean,
that is so fucked up.
So...
Are you getting married
next weekend?
I was. I was getting married,
but then I met you,
and now I don't...
Oh, my God!
No. Don't pull that shit.
(VOICE BREAKING) I feel fucking
stupid enough as it is.
So you're not a professor?
Are you even a photographer?
I'm a lawyer.
(LAUGHS)
I handle SEC compliance.
LLC agreements.
I came up here to...
Get the fuck out, Jason.
Seriously.
Can I have a second to explain?
No!
Hold up, hold up.
Not so fast, "Professor."
For what's it worth,
I still really
want to fuck you.
And we're going to fuck.
Yeah, we are.
We're going to thunder fuck.
You're gonna
tsunami on my face!
flood like the Nile.
Yeah. I guess the drought
in my pussy is finally over.
The villagers will finally eat.
You're gonna die
while you're eating me out.
I want your last breath
to be in my pussy.
Lenore! You're such a slut.
BOTH: Police! Shit!
That's right.
Po-po in the ho-ho.
OFFICER REITER:
Some kind of ganja party?
Sorry to harsh your mellows.
OFFICER FINCH:
Where's my e-vite?
Is that the jacket? Check the
right coat pocket. Check it, man.
Okay, turn around. Come on.
That's my jacket.
That's not his jacket.
OFFICER FINCH: Up against
the palm. There you go.
Let's have a look.
What've you got in here? Huh?
Bingo-bango. OMG.
What the fuck? That's not mine!
"What the fuck?"
That's not mine!
The fuck? Well, it looks
like Spring Break
is finally drug free!
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, pretty boy.
Oh, shall we?
No, it doesn't go down
that way. Let's go.
I'll wait for you, Grandpa.
DICK: Keep that shit
tight for me!
He's my Henry Miller.
What the fuck does that mean?
Exactly!
(DOOR BUZZING)
Hey, there he is.
You got blood on your
pants, you know.
Your license isn't
even suspended, is it?
You made all this up just so
I'd come down here with you.
I had to make sure you'd come.
Fuck you!
Just chill, Jason.
Hakuna matata.
JASON: Who the fuck are you?
I should have known
you were fucking crazy
the moment you started
hitting on women
the day after
Grandma's funeral!
Don't you fucking judge me.
You have no idea what I had
with your grandmother.
And everything I've done
these last few days
I've done for a reason.
You were about to fuck up
royally by getting married,
and you fucking know it!
Oh, yeah?
What the fuck am I
supposed to do now?
Chase around some college girl
that doesn't even want
to fucking talk to me?
Not know what the fuck I'm
doing for the rest of my life?
Yeah, because at least
you'd be thinking
for yourself for a change.
What the fuck
does that even mean?
Your father has lorded
over every decision
you've made in your adult life,
and Meredith is just
the latest example of that!
She's not right for you, Jason.
If you marry her, you're
going to be sleepwalking
through the rest of your life
and be completely unhappy,
just like your father!
I am already
unhappy with my life,
because I've done nothing
but get fucked by you
and this insane fuck rampage
that you've been on.
It wasn't a "fuck
rampage" for me.
It was a "fuck rampage" for you.
How? How is this for me?
I fucked up as a father.
I wasn't there
to raise your dad
and he turned into
a materialistic,
henpecked, poop-dick
country clubber.
I don't want that
to happen to you.
So that's what this was?
(SIGHS)
I was your last-ditch
redemption project.
Congratulations, Grandpa.
You thought you were
a shitty father?
Now you're
a shitty grandfather.
I don't want to
see you at my wedding.
Stay the fuck away from me.
(R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
So, do you like this
size, or this size?
(SIGHS)
Hey, hon, uh,
the people at the venue
said they don't have
enough mint napkins,
so which one
do you like better?
The seafoam or the pistachio?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I'll get it.
What is it?
Oh, it's, uh... Just
another wedding present.
I hope it's that
new big dipping spoon
from Williams-Sonoma.
And as a tribute
to Meredith and Jason
and the love
that you guys share.
A love I will never know
because my dog
died the first day
I masturbated.
So now I can't
get hard unless...
Okay.
Also, we've got to stop ISIS.
It's gotten... It's too much.
Got it. Got it.
You know, today's
celebration is much more
than just about the union
of two people,
it's also about the union
of two families.
Meredith...
The Kellys and the Goldsteins.
Let's have Jason and Meredith
tell their own story.
(ALL CHEERING)
NICK: Nice job, Uncle Dave!
(PLAYING SLOW MUSIC)
♪ For all those times
you stood by me
♪ For all the truth
that you made me see
♪ For all the joy
you brought to my life
♪ Into my life
♪ For all the wrong
that you made right
♪ For every dream
you made come true
♪ For all the love.
BOTH: ♪ I found in you
♪ I'll be...
♪ You've gotta be
forever thankful, baby
♪ You're the one
who held me up
♪ Never let me fall.
Let's go in for the kill.
♪ Through it all
(VOCALIZING)
You've been hacked.
♪ You were my strength
when I was weak
♪ You were my voice...
♪ When I couldn't speak
♪ You were my eyes
when I couldn't see
♪ You saw the best
there was in me
♪ Lifted me up
when I couldn't reach
(VOCALIZING)
♪ I'm everything I am
♪ Because you loved me ♪
Because you loved me.
(EXHALES)
What the fuck?
That is not Martha's Vineyard.
Jason!
Take it off!
Trying, dear. Trying.
Leave them on.
Shut it down.
I have something to say.
I think I've been listening
to everybody else
about what I should be
doing with my life.
My grandpa said something
really interesting.
All right, cut the mics.
I'm going up.
Take that punch,
that point forward,
things get easier.
The mic's off.
Jason, your mic cut out.
What?
Your mic cut out at the
most inopportune time,
so we can't hear
why you want to leave
those images up.
Hitting it won't work.
If they caught it
from the PA... Band?
What the fuck?
Nick, can you tell her
something for me?
Can you tell her that, uh...
I'm really sorry,
but I can't marry her.
You think that message should come from me?
Okay... Uh...
Uncle Ramon,
can you tell Meredith
that Jason's sorry,
but that they
can't get married?
(MOUTHING)
Oh, fuck!
I forgot Uncle Ramon was deaf
and I talked to him
like a normal.
Uncle Ruben,
can you please tell Meredith
that Jason is really sorry,
but that he can't marry her?
He says he's very sorry,
but he can't marry you.
Uncle Ruben,
can you turn
that thing up a little?
It doesn't get any louder.
Where'd you get
that thing, SkyMall?
At this point,
I'm kind of nervous
that anybody I pick
will have a disability.
Okay... Waiter... Hey, Pubes.
Can you please go tell Meredith
that my cousin Jason
is very sorry,
but they cannot get married?
Uh... Come on, man.
It's my first day here...
NICK: I know
it's your first day,
but everybody needs
you to be a man here.
Okay.
Just real quick...
He sent me... He wants me
to tell you that...
Um... (STAMMERS)
He doesn't think
that he can marry you.
But that he's sorry
that he can't.
(LAUGHING)
She's laughing, so I think
that you're in the clear, bro.
No, it's good. That was good.
You can just
go back and tell him
that I fucked his cousin
Nick while he was gone.
She's so super cool about it.
She's like, "Go!
Do your thing. Do you."
She said that?
NICK: That's what she said,
verbatim.
Wait. Should I come down
and say bye?
NICK: No. God! Fuck no!
No? Yeah.
No need to even...
Let's not even...
You just... I've done it...
We're great!
Wait, where the fuck
is he going?
Jason!
It's actually the guy on
the moped with the iPad.
NSA stopped using
utility vans years ago.
I figured once you sent
the camera back,
it was time to take
drastic measures.
What'd he say?
Are we doing this?
DICK: Plan B,
have Pam kidnap you.
I've got to get her back.
You want me to kidnap her?
I'll bring her back to you
in a box, bro.
She's on a bus headed west
on I-85 across Florida.
Her boat leaves in four hours.
It was easy to track her down
because of the whole
Middle Eastern thing.
Bet you never thought
you'd 69 a girl
because of the Patriot Act.
You 69 her, man!
And then she's dead.
Are you kidding me, Pam?
This is what you drive?
Oh, yeah, it is so easy
selling kids drugs
from an ice cream truck.
It's crazy!
Jason!
Jason! Go, go, go, go!
Jason, stop! Stop right now.
(ENGINE REVVING) Stop! Stop!
If you leave right now,
you can kiss your job
at the firm goodbye!
David, will you get
the fuck out of the way!
Hey, hey! Come on!
What the hell!
Hey, guy, unless you want
a Chipwich or some heroin,
get off my ice cream truck!
Who the fuck is this slob?
Slob? I am a small
business owner!
I am the backbone
of this country!
I am holding a taser!
(GROANS)
JASON: Whoa! Shit!
Dude, should I stop?
What are you... I'm kind of in
the middle of it right here.
Shit! All right. (THUDS)
(DICK CHUCKLING)
Raise your hand
if you've got a boner!
JASON: What were we
supposed to do?
Just leave him on the
side of the road?
Hey, man, can you slow down?
You're making this
very difficult.
What the fuck!
That was you who drew
all those dicks
on me last week?
Yeah, I drew the dicks.
Busted! Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
Don't worry. Get up. We'll cut
through the back roads.
Wait, what?
You navigate. I'll drive.
(HONKING)
Watch out! Watch out!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the hell is going on?
Whoa!
Got ourselves a bogey.
All right, let's do this!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Fuck! We gotta
lose some of this weight.
Pam, throw some
of this shit out of here!
Hey, look, it's Pam.
He's the good kind of Greek.
(BOTH PROTESTING)
Hey, Gene. Hey, Gary.
How the hell do you know
how to drive like that, Dad?
Damn it, Grandpa.
Just tell him!
Uh...
I was a Green Beret
in Special Forces.
I taught insurgents
behind enemy lines.
Mechanic was just my cover.
Good! We're all made up!
JASON: There they are!
That's them! Let's go, go, go!
Shadia! Jason?
Stop the bus!
I need to talk to you!
What are you doing here
in an ice cream truck?
Stop the bus!
Okay! Pull over!
I'm not pulling over!
Thanks a lot, Pam! You narc!
What! I'm not a narc, Barry!
Fuck you!
Pam, you know him?
Barry? Yeah, he's, like,
my best friend.
I sold him, like,
six tons of ecstasy... Oh!
That's why they're not
stopping the bus.
It's full of drugs.
Classic Pam.
I know that man. Stop the bus!
Jason, where are you going?
What are you doing?
What are they...
You'd better marry that girl.
Me? Nah, she's not really
my type. Too skinny.
What the fuck?
Slow down! Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Slow down, dude!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(CRASHING)
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go get her, man!
What is going on?
What just happened?
Hey. I don't even fucking know,
but I'm not getting married.
Okay, so that makes it okay
that you were lying to me?
JASON: No. No, it doesn't.
But you have to admit
when we were together
it felt great.
There was something real there.
Yeah.
What do you
want from me, Jason?
I want you to stay.
I just can't stay.
Okay. Okay.
No, I get it.
Yeah.
What if I come with you?
Come...
Really? I mean...
I just broke up with my
fiancee, lost my job.
And I think I'm wanted
by the police, so...
A year at sea
might actually be
the best place for me.
Okay.
Break it up, lesbians!
Let's go.
Get down on the ground!
We're doing this because
you're lesbians!
Get down on the ground!
According to
Interstate Statute 17.37,
arrests made on the
Interstate Highway System
must be executed
by state police,
not your local law enforcement
from your adjacent
municipalities.
You seem, like, really familiar
with the penal code.
You seem real cocksure
about the juris-dick-tion
you're in.
OFFICER REITER: Real cocksure!
Someone drew dicks all
over your face, you idiot!
OFFICER FINCH: Well, look at that!
You got dicks on your face.
That middle one's mine.
Look it, this one right here.
I traced it.
I thought I recognized that!
Enough catching up.
Let my friends go.
They've literally
done nothing wrong.
Pam, we've got obstruction
of justice here.
We got reckless endangerment.
The bus is full of drugs,
I get it.
Ooh, speaking of which,
I've got to get out of here.
I got three keys of "Frisbees"
showing up at the
store today, so...
I should go, question mark?
Why don't you
take my squad car.
That's a good idea.
Give him your keys.
You mean these keys?
There they are. (PAM LAUGHING)
Classic Pam. Classic Pam.
What do you say
we get some lunch?
Love it.
(ENGINE STARTS) (SIREN WAILING)
PAM: See you fucks later.
So, uh, I'm gonna go with her.
Yeah, you should.
She seems real nice.
You know, I think this is
our only way back now,
so I'm gonna try to get
these cocks off of my face
and get that truck started.
(CHUCKLES)
Just give me one sec. Yeah.
Grandpa...
Thank you for...
Don't give me any of that shit.
Just let me know
when you get back.
And I actually want to see
your photos in Time magazine.
This camera set me back three
months of my army pension.
Thanks, Grandpa.
Oh, and, Jason...
Yeah?
Back in the '80s,
when Andre the Giant
used to go to
the Playboy Mansion,
he'd stack five playmates
on top of each other on a bed
and fingerfuck them all.
Five at a time.
Because his hands were so big.
So...
That's it.
Thanks, Grandpa.
DICK: "De Oppresso Liber."
Motto of the Green Berets.
It means
"to liberate the oppressed."
Hey. You ready?
Yep.
I don't think he's gonna
find anybody as good as me.
I'm sorry. But you
know what they say...
Um...
"Tough times can sometimes
lead to tougher people."
Hmm. That's Kurt Vonnegut.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Holy fuckin' shit!
Has anyone ever told you that you
have the pussy of English Sheepdog?
Well, thanks for the ride.
You gonna be okay, Dad?
I miss her.
But I'll be okay.
I was a shitty father
and I'm sorry.
Well, we'll work on it.
You're a hard man
to track down, Professor.
Are those my pants?
Yeah, these are your pants.
I found a Werther's
Original in the pocket
and I've been sucking
on it all morning.
You do know that I'm not
a professor, right?
Yeah, I know.
You're just a dirty,
dirty grandpa,
and I'm just a girl
from Long Island City
who likes to fuck old people.
I like your pull-out couch.
Yeah, well, I got news for you.
That's the only thing that's
gonna be pulling out tonight.
I'll be right back.
Oh, hey.
Look, I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can do this.
I haven't done it
for a long time.
Whoops! I guess
they just slipped off.
I want you to tear open my bra
like it's a social
security check.
Tell me you've fallen
and you can't get up.
"Help, I've fallen
and I can't get up."
Oh, no!
Now fumble around and pretend
like you're trying
to find your glasses.
"I'm trying to find
my glasses. I can't see."
"I found them!
I can see! I can see!"
Tell me it's 4:00
and you want to eat dinner.
"It's 4:00 and
I want to eat dinner."
Tell me the buttons
on your remote control
are so small that
you can't find Fox News.
"The buttons
on my remote control"
"are so small
I can't find Fox News!"
Tell me how small they are!
"They're real small!"
Tell me how this
neighborhood used to be safer!
"This neighborhood
used to be safer!"
Tell me how things were
better under Eisenhower!
"Things were better
under Eisenhower!"
We like Ike! We like Ike!
We like Ike!
BOTH: We like Ike!
(DICK YELLING)
LENORE: Are you
cumming or dying?
DICK: I'm not sure! Maybe both!
(BOTH PANTING)
(1950s MUSIC PLAYING)
"...for as by a man came death."
"By a man has come also life."
Richard Kelly II.
Congratulations on the
baby's new godparents,
- Jason and Shadia.
ALL: Aw!
MAN: Congratulations!
Back to Mommy. All baptized.
Man, you just keep
surprising me, Grandpa.
New dad at 72.
Great fucking idea.
Hey, watch your potty mouth!
Jesus, sorry... Yeah,
clean up your language.
And show some respect
for your new grandmother!
I'm sorry, honey.
That's all right.
And sweetie, would it kill
you to visit us sometimes?
We never see you.
Sorry, Nanna.
Did you get that card
I sent for your birthday?
Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, with the $12 check.
That was a very nice touch.
Thank you.
Thank you. That's right.
Hey, what are you,
gaining some weight?
You look a little
heavy in the face.
No, what are you... Where'd
this come from, huh?
What? Where'd these
guys come from?
You wanna go get the car?
Okay. Yeah.
All right, I'll pull
around the minivan.
Go to Daddy.
There we go, come to Daddy.
It's you and I.
It's a little bit weird.
She's my grandma.
And you're my uncle.
Look at that. Holy shit!
It's a good dick.
Oh, my God! Put that away.
It's our dick. Yeah.
I'm just relieved
it's not his dick.
You want to get
the bottle for me?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, how you doin' there?
(PAM MIMICS FARTING)
(LAUGHING)
Hey, Jason. You should
check your diaper, bro.
I think you just
shit your pants.
And in church, too,
in front of God.
I don't get why you're here.
(MIMICS FARTING)
Oh! Someone made
a doodie in their yum-yum.
I'm just gonna
put this out there once.
I know your baby
just got baptized,
but I've got a guy in Tampa who
will pay upwards of 60 grand
for a healthy, white,
male baby that can fight.
This is a good deal.
You should take it.
I don't know
this guy that well,
but he seems
extremely trustworthy.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You interested? Classic Pam.
Classic Pam.
Knock, knock. Who's there?
Classic Pam. (LAUGHING)
Guess it's never too late
to start over, huh?
Yeah. Nice to have
a second chance.
Maybe it won't take me so long to get
the father thing right this time.
Right?
I'll go get his car seat.
Jamba!
(LAUGHTER)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org