Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
ZOOTOPIA
Fear, treachery, blood lust.
Thousands of years ago
these were the...
forces that ruled our world
A world where prey were
scared of predators.
And predators had an
uncontrollable...
biological urge to maim, and maul, and...
Awww!
Blood! Blood! Blood!
And.. death!
Ahhh...
Back then, the world
was divided in two.
Vicious predator,
or meek prey.
But over time, we evolved,
and moved beyond or primitive savage ways.
Now predator and prey
live in harmony.
And every young mammal
has multitudinous opportunities.
Yeah, I don't have to cower
in a a herd anymore.
Instead, I can be an astronaut.
I don't have to be a lonely hunter anymore.
Today I can hunt for tax exemptions.
I'm gonna be an actuary.
And I can make the world a better place.
I am going to be...
A police officer!
Bunny cop? That is the most
stupidest thing I ever heard!
It may seem impossible to small minds.
I'm looking at you, Gideon Grey.
But, just 211 miles away,
stands the great city of Zootopia.
Where our ancestors first joined
together in peace.
And declared that anyone
can be anything!
Thank you and good night.
Judy, you ever wonder how your mom
and me got to be so darn happy?
Nope
Well, we gave up on our dreams,
and we settled. Right, Bon?
Oh, yes. That's right, Stu.
We settled hard.
You see, that's the beauty
of complacency, Jude.
If you don't try anything
new, you'll never fail.
I like trying, actually.
What your father means, hon, is that it's
gonna be difficult, impossible even...
- for you to become a police officer.
- Right. There's never been a bunny cop.
- No.
- Bunnies don't do that.
- Never.
Well... Then I guess
I'll have to be the first one.
Because I am gonna make
the world a better place!
Or, heck, you know. You wanna talk
about making the world a better place,
no better way to do it than
becoming a carrot farmer.
Yes! Your dad, me,
your 275 brothers and sisters.
- We're changing the world.
- Yeah.
- One carrot at a time.
- Amen to that.
Carrot farming is a noble profession.
You get it, honey?
I mean, it's great to have dreams.
Yeah, just as long as you
don't believe in them too much.
Where the heck'd she go?
Give me your tickets right now,
or I'm gonna kick your meek little sheep butt.
Ow! Cut it out, Gideon!
Baah, baah!
What are you gonna do, cry?
- Hey! You heard her. Cut it out.
- Nice costume, loser.
What crazy world are you living in
where you think a bunny could be a cop?
- Kindly return my friend's tickets.
- Come and get them. But watch out.
Cause I'm a fox, and like you said
in your dumb little stage play,
us predators used to eat prey.
And that killer instinct's still in our denna.
- Uh, I'm pretty much sure it's pronounced DNA.
- Don't tell me what I know, Travis.
You don't scare me, Gideon.
Scared now?
Look at her nose twitch,
she is scared.
Cry, little baby bunny!
Cry... Ow...
Oh, you don't know
when to quit, do you?
Huh!
I want you to remember this moment
the next time you think you will ever be...
anything more than just a
stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
- That looks bad.
- Are you okay, Judy?
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Here you go.
- Wow, you got our tickets!
- You're awesome, Judy.
Yeah, that Gideon Grey doesn't know
what he's talking about!
Well, he was right
about one thing.
I don't know when to quit.
ZOOTOPIA POLICE ACADEMY
Listen up, cadets. Zootopia has 12
unique ecosystems within its city limits.
Tundratown, Sahara Square,
Rainforest District, to name a few.
You're gonna have to master all of
them before you hit the streets.
Or guess what?
You'll be dead!
Scorching sandstorm.
You're dead, bunny bumpkin.
One thousand foot fall.
You're dead, carrot face.
Frigid ice wall.
You're dead, farm girl.
Enormous criminal.
You're dead.
Dead.
Ohhh...!
Filthy toilet.
You're dead, fluff butt.
Just quit and go home, fuzzy bunny.
- There's never been a bunny cop. Never.
- Just a stupid carrot-farming dumb bunny.
As mayor of Zootopia, I am proud
to announce that my mammal inclusion...
initiative, has produced its first
police academy graduate.
Valedictorian of her class,
ZPD's very first rabbit officer...
Judy Hopps.
Assistant Mayor Bellwether, her badge.
- Oh, yes, yes!
- Thank you.
Judy, it is my great privilege to officially
assign you to the heart of Zootopia...
Precinct One.
City Center.
- Yeh!
Congratulations Officer Hopps.
I won't let you down.
This has been my dream
since I was a kid.
You know, it's a real proud
day for us little guys.
Bellwether, make room, will you?
Okay, Officer Hopps.
Let's see those teeth!
Officer Hopps, look here.
- We're real proud of you, Judy.
- Yeah, and scared too.
- Yes.
- Really, it's kind of a proud-scared combo.
I mean, Zootopia.
So far away, such a big city.
Guys, I've been working for this
my whole life.
We know. And we're just a little
exited for you, but terrified.
The only thing we have to
fear is fear itself.
And also bears. We have
bears to fear, too.
- Say nothing on lions, and wolves.
- Wolves?
- Weasels.
- You played cribbage with a weasel once?
Yeah, he cheats like
there's no tomorrow.
You know what?
Pretty much all predators.
- And Zootopia is full of them.
- Oh, Stu.
And foxes are the worst.
Yeah, actually, your father
does have a point there.
It's in their biology.
Remember what happened with Gideon Grey?
When I was nine. Gideon Grey was
a jerk who happens to be a fox.
I know plenty of bunnies who are jerks.
Sure, yeah, we all do, absolutely.
But just in case,
we made you a little
care package to take with you.
- I put some snacks in there.
- This is fox deterrent.
- Yeah, it's safe to have that.
- This is fox repellant.
The deterrent and the
repellant, that's all she needs.
- Check this out!
- Oh, for goodness sake!
She has no need for
a fox taser, Stu.
Oh, come on.
When is there not a need for a fox taser?
Well, okay, look, I will take this...
To make you stop talking.
Terrific!
Everyone wins!
Arriving, Zootopia Express.
Okay, gotta go.
Bye!
Mmm. I love you, guys.
Love you, too.
- Oh, cripes, here come the waterworks.
- Oh, Stu. Pull it together.
Bye everybody!
Bye Judy, I love you!
Bye!
YOU ARE NOW LEAVING
BUNNYBURROW.
♪ Oh oh oh oh ooh ♪
♪ I messed up tonight
I lost another fight ♪
♪ I still mess up but I'll just start again ♪
♪ I keep falling down
I keep on hitting the ground ♪
♪ I always get up now to see what's next ♪
♪ Birds don't just fly
They fall down and get up ♪
♪ Nobody learns without getting it wrong ♪
♪ I won't give up, no I won't give in ♪
♪ Till I reach the end
And then I'll start again ♪
♪ No I won't leave
I wanna try everything ♪
♪ I wanna try even though I could fail ♪
♪ I won't give up, no I won't give in ♪
♪ Till I reach the end
And then I'll start again ♪
♪ No I won't leave
I wanna try everything ♪
♪ I wanna try even though I could fail ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ooh
Try everything ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ooh ♪
♪ I'll keep on making those new mistakes ♪
♪ I'll keep on making them every day ♪
♪ Those new mistakes ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ooh
Try everything ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ooh ♪
♪ Try everything ♪
I'm Gazelle.
Welcome to Zootopia.
And welcome to the Grand Pangolin Arms.
Luxury apartments with charm.
Complementary delousing once a month.
Don't lose your key!
Thank you.
- Oh, hi! I'm Judy, your new neighbor!
- Yeah? Well, we're loud.
Don't expect us to apologize for it.
Greasy walls.
Rickety bed.
Crazy neighbors.
I love it!
Come on!
He bared his teeth first!
- Excuse me!
- Hmm?
Down here!
- Hi.
- O... M... Goodness!
They really did hire a bunny.
Ho-whop! I gotta tell you,
you're even cuter than I thought you'd be.
Ooh, ah, you probably didn't know,
but a bunny can call another bunny "cute",
but when other animals
do it, that's a little...
Ohhh. I am so sorry!
Me, Benjamin Clawhauser.
The guy everyone thinks is just
a flabby donut-loving cop, stereotyping you.
- Oh.
- No, it's okay.
Oh. You've actually got...
there's a...
- A what?
- In your neck. The fold.
- The... this...
- Oh, there you went, you little dickens!
Hehehe, I should get to roll call,
so which way do I...
- Oh, ball pen's over there to the left.
- Great. Thank you!
Oh... That poor little bunny's gonna
get eaten alive.
Hey! Officer Hopps.
You ready to make the world a better place?
Attention!
All right. All right.
Everybody sit.
I've got three items
on the docket.
First, we need to acknowledge
the elephant in the room.
Francine.
Happy birthday.
Oh.
Number two. There are some new recruits
with us I should introduce,
but I'm not going to because...
I don't care.
Finally, we have 14 missing mammal cases.
All predators. From a giant polar bear
to a teensy little otter.
And City Hall is right up
my tail to find them.
This is priority number one.
Assignments.
Officers Grizzoli, Fragmire, Delgato.
Your team take missing mammals
from the Rainforest District.
Officers McHorn, Rhinowitz, Wolfard.
Your teams take Sahara Square.
Officers Higgins, Snarlov, Trunkaby.
Tundratown.
And finally, our first bunny,
Officer Hopps.
Parking duty.
Dismissed.
Parking duty?
Chief?
Chief Bogo?
Sir. You said there were
fourteen missing mammal cases.
- So?
- So I can handle one.
You probably forgot but, I was
top of my class at the academy.
Didn't forget.
Just don't care.
Sir, I'm not just
some token bunny.
Well then, writing a hundred
tickets a day should be easy.
A 100 tickets. I'm not
gonna write 100 tickets.
I'm gonna write 200 tickets.
Before noon.
FREQUENT STOPS
(EXPIRED)
Ah!
Boom!
Two hundred tickets before noon!
201.
Hey, watch where you're going, fox!
Huh!
Hmm.
Where'd he go?
Listen. I know what you're doing
skulking around during daylight hours,
but I don't want any
trouble in here. So hit the road!
I'm not looking for
any trouble either, sir...
I simply wanna buy a Jumbo-Pop.
For my little boy.
You want the red,
or the blue, pal?
Oh.
I'm such a...
- Oh, come on, kid. Back up. Listen, buddy.
- What?
There aren't any fox ice cream joints
in your part of town?
No, no. There are, there are.
It's just, my boy,
this goofy little stinker,
he loves all things elephant.
He wants to be one
when he grows up.
Isn't that adorable?
Who the heck am I to crush
his little dreams, huh? Right?
Look, you probably can't read, fox,
but the sign says
We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone!
So beat it.
You're holding up the line.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Hey, you're gonna have to wait your
turn like everyone else, meter maid.
Actually, I'm an officer.
Just have a quick question.
Are your customers
aware they're getting
snot and mucus with
their cookies and cream?
What are you talking about?
Well. I don't wanna
cause you any trouble,
but I believe scooping ice cream with an
ungloved trunk is a class 3 health code violation.
Which is kind of a big deal.
Of course I could let you off with
a warning if you were to glove those trunks
and... I don't know...
finish selling this...
nice dad and his son a...
What was it?
A Jumbo-Pop.
Please.
- $15.
- Thank you so much. Thank you.
Oh no, are you kidding me...
I don't have my wallet!
I'd lose my head if it
weren't attached to my neck.
That's the truth. Oh, boy.
I'm sorry, pal.
Gotta be about the
worst birthday ever.
Please don't be mad at me.
Thanks anyway.
Keep the change.
Officer, I can't thank you enough.
So kind. Really. Can I pay you back?
Oh, no.
My treat.
It's just, you know it burns me up to see folks
with such backward attitudes towards foxes.
I just want to say you're a great
dad and just a real articulate fella.
Oh.
Well, that is high praise.
It's rare that I find
someone so non-patronizing.
- Officer?
- Hopps. Mr..?
Wilde.
Nick Wilde.
And you, little guy. You wanna
be an elephant when you grow up?
You be an elephant.
Because this is Zootopia.
Anyone can be anything.
Ahh.
I tell him that all the time.
All right, here you go.
Two paws.
Yeah. Oh, look at that smile,
that's a happy birthday smile!
All right, give her a little
bye-bye toot-toot.
Toot-toot.
- Bye, now!
- Goodbye!
Oh.
Hey, little toot-toot...
"ORGANIC"  $2
PAWPSICLE
"ORGANIC " *$2
LEMMING
BROTHERS
BANK
Get your Pawpsicles.
Oh!
- Lumber delivery.
- What's with the color?
The color?
Uh... it's redwood.
39, 40, there you go.
Way to work that diaper, big guy.
Hey. No kiss
bye-bye for daddy?
You kiss me tomorrow,
I'll bite your face off!
Ciao.
Well, I stood up for you,
and you lied to me.
You liar!
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart.
And I'm not the liar. He is.
Hey!
All right, Slick-Nick.
You're under arrest.
Really?
For what?
Gee, I don't know. How about
selling food without a permit?
Transporting undeclared commerce
across borough lines?
- False advertizing.
- Permit. Receipt of declared commerce.
And I didn't falsely
advertize anything. Take care.
You told that mouse the
Pawpsicle sticks were redwood!
That's right. Red wood.
With a space in the middle.
Wood that is red.
You can't touch me, Carrots.
I've been doing this since I was born.
You're gonna wanna refrain
from calling me Carrots.
My bad. I just naturally
assumed you came...
from some little carrot-choked Podunk.
No?
Uh, no. Podunk is in Deerbrooke county
and I grew up in Bunnyburrow.
Okay.
Tell me if this story sounds familiar.
Naive little hick with good
grades and big ideas decides
"Hey, look at me, I'm
gonna move to Zootopia...
Where predators and prey live
in harmony and sing Kumbaya!"
Only to find, whoopsie,
we don't all get along.
And that dream of becoming a big city cop,
double whoopsie, she's a meter maid.
And whoopsie number three-sie,
no one cares about her or her dreams.
And soon enough those dreams die, and our
bunny sinks into emotional and literal squalor
living in a box under a bridge. Till finally she has no choice but to go
back home
with that cute fuzzy wuzzy little tail
between her legs to become...
You're from Bunnyburrow, is that what you said?
So how about a carrot farmer?
That sound about right?
Oh!
Be careful now, or it won't just
be your dreams getting crushed.
Hey, hey. No one tells me what I can
or can't be. Especially not some...
jerk who never had the guts to try to be
anything more than a Pawpsicle hustler.
All right, look.
Everyone comes to Zootopia thinking
they can be anything they want.
Well, you can't.
You can only be what you are.
Sly fox.
Dumb bunny.
I'm not a dumb bunny.
Right.
And that's not wet cement.
You'll never be a real cop.
You're a cute meter maid, though.
Maybe a supervisor one day.
Hang in there.
♪ Everybody hurts... ♪
♪ ..by myself... ♪
♪ You can't do nothing right, baby... ♪
♪ I'm a loser... ♪
CARROTS for ONE
Mom & Dad
- Oh, hey, it's my parents!
- Oh, there she is! Hi, Sweetheart!
Hey there, Jude the Dude.
How was your first day on the force?
- It was real great!
- Yeah? Everything you ever hoped?
Absolutely. And more.
Everyone's so nice, and I feel like...
- I'm really making a difference.
- Wait a second. Holy cranks, Bonnie.
- Look at that!
- Oh, my sweet heaven!
Judy, are you a meter maid?
Oh, this.. No! Oh, no.
This is just a temporary thing..
- It's the safest job on the force!
- She's not a real cop!
- Our prayers have been answered!
- Glorious day!
Ho-ho, meter maid,
meter maid, meter maid!
- Dad! Dad!
- Meter maid!
You know what,
it's been a really long day, I should...
- You get some rest.
- Those meters aren't gonna maid themselves.
- Bye-bye.
Hey, bunny!
Turn down that depressing music!
Leave the meter maid alone,
didn't you hear her conversation?
- She feels like a failure!
- Oh, shut up!
- You shut up!
- Tomorrow is another day.
Yeah, but it might be worse!
I was 30 seconds over!
Yeah, you're a real hero, lady.
My mommy says
she wishes you were dead.
Uncool rabbit, my tax dollars
pay your salary.
I am a real cop.
Hey, you!
Bunny!
Sir, if you have a grievance you may
contest recitation in traffic court.
What are you talking about?!
My shop!
It was just robbed!
Look, he's getting away!
Well, are you a cop or not?
Oh! Yes! Yes!
Don't worry, sir, I got this!
- Stop in the name of the law!
- Catch me if ya' can, cottontail!
Coming through!
This is officer McHorn.
We got a 10-31.
I got dibs!
Officer Hopps, I am in pursuit!
Woo-hoo!
LITTLE
RODENTIA
- Ah!
- Ahh!
Ha ha ha.
You!
Hey!
Hey, meter maid!
Wait for the real cops!
Stop!
Ahhhh!
Oh.
Sorry! Coming through.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Pardon.
Yahhh!
Bon voyage, flatfoot!
Huh!
- Hey! Stop right there!
- Have a donut, coppa!
Oh my god, did you see those
leopard print jeggings?
- Ah!
Oh!
- I love your hair.
- Thank you.
Heheheheh.
Come to papa!
Okay. You're gonna have
to be patient and wait in line
just like everyone else,
Mrs. Otterton. Okay?
- I popped the weasel!
- Hopps!
Abandoning your post. Inciting a scurry.
Reckless endangerment of rodents...
But, to be fair, you did stop a master criminal
from stealing two dozen moldy onions.
Mmm. Hate to disagree with you, sir,
but those aren't onions.
Those are a crocus variety called
midnicampum holicithias.
They're a class C botanical, sir.
Well, I grew up in a family where plant
husbandry was kind of a thing...
- Shut your tiny mouth now!
- Sir, I got the bad guy.
That's my job.
Your job is putting tickets
on parked cars!
Chief, Mrs. Otterton's
here to see you again.
- Not now.
- Okay, I just need to know if you want to...
- take it this time she seems really upset...
- Not now!
Sir. I don't wanna
be a meter maid,
I wanna be a real cop.
Do you think the mayor
asked what I wanted...
- when he assigned you to me?
- But, sir...
Life isn't some cartoon musical where you
sing a little song, and your insipid dreams...
magically come true!
So let it go.
Chief Bogo, please!
Five minutes of your time, please.
I'm sorry sir. I tried to stop her,
she's super slippery.
I gotta go sit down.
Ma'am, as I've told you,
we're doing everything we can.
My husband has been
missing for ten days.
- His name is Emmitt Otterton.
- Yes. I know.
He's a florist.
We have 2 beautiful children.
He would never just disappear.
Ma'am, our detectives
are very busy.
Please. There's gotta be somebody
to find my Emmitt.
- Mrs. Otterton.
- I will find him.
Oh. Thank you!
Bless you, bless you, little bunny!
Take this.
Find my Emmitt.
Bring him home to me and my babies.
Please.
Mrs. Otterton.
Please wait out here.
Of course.
Oh, thank you both so much!
One second.
- You're fired.
- What? Why?
Insubordination! Now. I'm going to open
this door, and you're goind to tell that Otter
you're a former meter maid with delusion
of grandeur, who will not be taking the case.
I just heard Officer Hopps
is taking the case!
Assistant Mayor Bellwether!
The Mammal Inclusion Initiative
is really starting to pay off.
Mayor Lionheart is
just gonna be so jazzed!
No, let's not tell
the mayor just yet.
And I sent it, and it is done,
so I did do that.
All right, well, I'd say
the case is in good hands.
Us little guys really need to
stick together, right?
- Like glue.
- Good one.
Just call me if you ever
need anything. Okay?
You've always got a friend at
City Hall, Judy. All right! Bye-bye!
Thank you, ma'am!
I will give you 48 hours.
Yes!
That's two days to find Emmitt Otterton.
But.. You strike out, you resign.
Okay. Deal.
Splendid. Clawhauser will give you
the complete case file.
Here you go.
One missing otter.
- That's it?
- Yikes!
That is the smallest case file
I've ever seen. Leads, none.
Witnesses, none. And you're not in the
computer system yet, so...
Resources, none!
Ha ha!
Hoo, I hope you didn't stake your
career on cracking this one.
Okay.
Last known sighting.
Can I just borrow?
Thank you.
- Pawpsicle?
- The murder weapon!
- "Get your Pawpsicle"...
- Yeah! Cause that...
What does that mean?
It means I have a lead.
- Hi! Hello! It's me again!
- Hey! It's officer toot-toot.
Hoo...No.
Actually it's Officer Hopps,
and I'm here to ask you some
questions about a case.
What happened, meter maid?
Did someone steal a traffic cone?
It wasn't me.
Hey, Carrots, you're gonna wake the baby.
I gotta get to work.
This is important, sir. I think your
ten dollars worth of Pawpsicles can wait.
Ha! I make 200 bucks
a day, fluff.
365 days a year,
since I was 12.
- And time is money. Hop along.
- Please just look at the picture.
You sold Mr. Otterton that Pawpsicle, right?
- Do you know him?
- I know everybody.
And I also know that somewhere
there's a toy store missing its stuffed animal,
so why don't you get back to your box?
Fine.
Then we'll have to do this the hard way.
- Did you just boot my stroller?
- Nicholas Wilde, you are under arrest.
Ha. For what? Hurting
your feelings?
Felony tax evasion.
Yeah.. 200 dollars a day, 365 days a year,
since you were 12...
that's two decades, so times twenty, which is
1,460,000, I think.
I mean, I am just a dumb bunny,
but we are good at multiplying.
Anyway, according to your tax forms,
you reported, let me see here, zero!
Unfortunately, lying on a federal form
is a punishable offense.
- 5 years jail time.
- Well, it's my word against yours.
200 bucks a day, fluff,
365 days a year, since I was twelve.
Actually it's your
word against yours.
And if you want this pen
you're going to help me
find this poor missing otter,
or the only place
you'll be selling Pawpsicles
is the prison cafeteria.
It's called a hustle, sweet heart.
She hustled you.
Ehahaha...
She hustled you good!
You're a cop now, Nick.
You're gonna need one of these.
Have fun working with the fuzz!
Start talking.
I don't know where he is,
I only saw where he went.
Great, let's go!
It's not exactly a place
for a cute little bunny.
- Don't call me cute, get in the car.
- Okay. You're the boss.
Hi.
I'm...
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Hello!
My name is...
You know, I'm gonna hit the
pause button right there.
Cause we're all good on
bunny scout cookies.
Uh, no.
I'm Officer Hopps, ZPD.
I'm looking for a missing mammal...
Emmitt Otterton. Right here.
He may have frequented this establishment?
Yeah, old Emmitt!
Haven't seen him in
a couple of weeks.
But hey, you should talk to his yoga instructor.
I'd be happy to take you back.
Oh, thank you so much, I'd appericiate
that more than you can imagine, it'd be such...
- Oh! You are naked..
- Oh, for sure. We're a naturalist club!
Yeah. In Zootopia anyone can be anything.
These guys, they be naked.
Nangi's just on the other side
of the pleasure pool.
Oh boy. Does this make you uncomfortable?
Because if so, there's no shame in calling it quits.
Yes, there is.
Boy, that's the spirit.
Yeah, some mammals say the naturalist life is weird.
But you know what I say is weird?
Clothes on animals!
Here we go!
As you can see, Nangi is an elephant,
so she'll totally remember everything.
Hey, Nangi. These dudes have some questions
about Emmitt the otter.
- Who?
- Eh.
Emmitt Otterton. Been coming
to your yoga class for like six years.
I have no memory
of this beaver.
He's an otter, actually.
He was here a couple of
Wednesdays ago. Remember?
No.
Yeah, he was wearing a green
cable knit sweater vest,
and a new pair of Quarterway slacks.
Oh, and a Paisley tie, sweet Windsor knot.
- Real tight. Remember that, Nangi?
- No.
Yeah, and we both walked him out, and he got into this
big old white car with a silver trim.
Needed a tune up. The third cylinder
wasn't firing. Remember that, Nangi?
No.
Eh. You didn't happen to catch
the licence plate number?
- Did you?
- Oh, for sure. It was 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
0-3. Wow, this is a lot of great info.
Thank you.
Told you Nangi has a mind like a steel trap.
I wish I had a memory like an elephant.
Well, I had a ball. You are welcome for the clue.
And seeing as any moron can run a plate,
I will take that pen
and bid you adieu.
The plate.
I can't run a plate.
Oomf.
I'm not in the system yet.
- Give me the pen, please.
- What was it you said?
Any moron can run a plate?
Gosh, if only there were a moron around
who were up to the task.
Rabbit, I did what you asked.
You can't keep me
on the hook forever.
Not forever. Well, I only have 36
hours left to solve this case.
So can you run the plate or not?
Actually, I just remembered,
I have a pal at the DMV.
Flash is the fastest guy in there.
You need something done, he's on it.
I hope so. We are really fighting the clock
and every minute counts.
Wait.
They're all sloths?
You said this was
going to be quick!
What, are you saying just
because he's a sloth
he can't be fast? I thought in
Zootopia anyone could be anything.
Flash, Flash, Hundred Yard Dash!
Buddy, it's nice to see you.
Nice to... see you... too.
Hey, Flash, I'd love
you to meet my friend.
Ah...Darlin, I've forgotten your name.
Hmm. Officer Judy Hopps, ZPD.
How are you?
I am...
doing... just..
- Fine?
- as well.. as..  I can.. be...
- What...
- Hang in there.
- can I... do...
- Well, I was hoping you could run a plate...
- for you...
- Well, I was hoping you could...
...today?
Well, I was hoping you could run a plate for us.
We are in a really big hurry.
- Sure... What's the... plate...
- 2-9-T...
- Number?
- 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
- 2... 9...
- T-H-D-0-3.
- T...
- H-D-0-3.
- H...
- D-0-3.
- D...
- Mm-hm. 0-3.
- 0...
- 3!
- Hey, Flash. Wanna hear a joke?
- No!
- Sure.
- Mmm!
What do you call a
three-humped camel?
I don't know.
What do you call...
-  Three-humped camel.
- a three-humped... camel?
Pregnant.
Ha ha ha ha...
Ha ha. Yes, very funny, very funny!
Can we please just focus on the task?
- Hey...
- Wait, wait!
- Priscilla!
- Oh, no!
- Yes... Flash?
- What... do..
- No...
- you call...
A three-humped camel?
- Pregnant! Okay! We got it! Please just...
- - three... humped...
- Here... you...
- Yes! Yeah, yeah! Hurry, thank you!
- 2-9-T-H-D-0-3.
- ...go.
It's registered to
Tundratown Limo Service.
A limo took Otterton! And
the limo's in Tundratown!
It's in Tundratown!
Way to hustle, bud. I love you.
I owe you.
Hurry! We gotta beat the rush hour and...
It's night?!
Closed.
Great.
Mm. And I will betcha
you don't have a warrant to get in, hmm?
- Darn it. It's a bummer.
- You wasted the day on purpose.
Ma'am, I have a fake badge. I would never
impede your pretend investigation.
It's not a pretend investigation!
Look, see? See him? This otter is missing.
Well, then they should have
gotten a real cop to find him.
What is your problem? Does
seeing me fail somehow make
you feel better about your
own sad, miserable life?
It does, 100%.
Now, since you're sans warrant.
I guess we're done?
Fine. We are done.
Here's your pen.
First off, you throw like a bunny.
Second, you're a very sore loser.
See you later, Officer Fluff.
So sad this is over.
- I wish I could have helped more.
- The thing is, you don't need...
a warrant if you have probable cause,
and I'm pretty sure I saw a...
shifty lowlife climbing the fence.
So you're helping plenty! Come on!
2-9-T-H-D-0-3!
This is it!
Polar bear fur.
- Oh my God!
- What? What?
The Velvety Pipes of Jerry Vole!
But on CD.
Who still uses CDs?
Carrots, if your otter was here,
he had a very bad day.
Those are claw marks.
You ever seen anything like this?
- No.
- Oh, wait. Look!
This is him. Emmitt Otterton.
He was definitely here.
What do you think happened?
Oh no, wait a minute.
Polar bear fur...
Rat-pack music. Fancy cup.
I know whose car this is, we gotta go!
- What? Whose car is it?
- The most feared crime boss in Tundratown.
They call him Mr. Big, and he does not
like me. So we gotta go!
I'm not leaving,
this is a crime scene.
Well, it's gonna be an
even bigger crime scene...
if Mr. Big finds me here,
so we're leaving right now.
Raymond! And is that Kevin?
Long time, no see.
And speaking of no see,
how about you forget you saw me?
Huh?
For old times sake?
That's a no..
What did you do that made
Mr. Big so mad at you?
I, uh... I may have sold him
a very expensive wall rug
that was made from the fur
of a skunk's butt.
Oh, sweet cheese 'n crackers.
- Is that Mr. Big?
- No.
- What about him? Is that him?
- That's gotta be him.
- Stop talking. Stop talking. Stop talking!
Huh.
Mr. Big, sir,
this is a simple misunder...
Hmmph.
Yeah.
This is a simple misunderstanding.
You come here unannounced on the
day my daughter is to be married.
Well, actually, we were brought here
against our will, so...
Point is, I did not know
that it was your car,
and I certainly did not know about
your daughter's wedding!
I trusted you, Nicky.
I welcomed you into my home.
We broke bread together.
Grandmama made you a cannoli.
And how did you repay my generosity?
With a rug
made from the butt of a skunk.
A skunk-butt rug.
You disrespected me.
You disrespected my grandmama,
who I buried in that skunk-butt rug.
I told you never to show your face
here again, but here you are.
Snooping around with this...
What are you? A performer?
What's with the costume?
- Sir, I am a co...
- Mime!
She's a mime.
This mime can not speak.
- You can't speak if you're a mime.
- No, I am a cop.
And I'm on the Emmitt Otterton case.
And my evidence puts him in your car!
So intimidate me all you want,
I'm going to find out what you did to that otter
if it's the last thing I do.
Hmm.
Then I have only one request.
Say hello to Grandmama.
Ice 'em!
No, no, no. I didn't see nothing!
I'm not saying nothing!
And you never will.
Please!
No, no, no, no!
If you're mad at me about
the rug, I've got more rugs!
Daddy! It's time for our dance!
Ah! What did we say?
No icing anyone at my wedding!
I have to, baby,
daddy has to.
- Ice 'em.
- No, no, no!
Wait, wait!
She's the bunny that saved my life yesterday!
From that giant donut!
- This bunny?
- Yeah. Hi!
- Hi. I love your dress.
- Oh. Thank you.
Put them down.
You've done me a great service.
I will help you find the otter.
I will take your kindness,
and pay it forward.
Hmm.
Otterton is my florist.
He's like a part of the family.
He had something important
he wanted to discuss.
That's why I sent that
car to pick him up.
But he never arrived.
Because he was attacked.
No, he attacked.
Otterton?
Otterton.
He went crazy.
Ripped up the car.
Scared my driver half to death.
And disappeared into the night.
But he's a sweet little otter.
My child, we may be evolved,
but deep down we are still animals.
You wanna find Otterton, talk to
the driver of the car.
His name is Manchas.
Lives in the Rainforest District.
Only he can tell you more.
Mr. Manchas?
Judy Hopps, ZPD.
We just wanna know what happened
to Emmitt Otterton.
You should be asking
what happened to me.
- Whoa. A teensy otter did that?
- What happened?
He was an animal.
Down on all fours.
He was a savage!
There was no warning.
He just kept yelling about the Night Howlers.
Over and over, the Night Howlers!
So you know about
the Night Howlers too?
Good, good.
Because the Night Howlers are exactly
what we are here
to talk about. Right?
Yes, so you just open the
door and tell us what you know,
and we will tell you what we know.
Okay?
Okay.
Clever fox.
Mr. Manchas?
Are you okay?
Run. Run!
- What is wrong with him?!
- I don't know!
Jump!
Come on!
Head down!
Officer Hopps to dispatch!
Are you familiar with Gazelle? Greatest
singer of our lifetime. Angel with horns.
Okay, hold on.
Keep watching.
Who's that beside her?
Who is it?
Wow, you are one hot dancer,
Benjamin Clawhauser.
It's me! Did you think it was real?
It looks so real!
It's not, it's just a new app.
- Hold on a second.
- Clawhauser!
Clawhauser, listen to me.
We have a 10-91!
Jaguar gone savage!
- Vine and Tujunga!
- It's Tu-hunga!
Okay, we're sending backup!
Look, over there!
Head for the sky-trans!
Get in.
Carrots? Carrots!
Go!
Buddy, one predator to another.
Now I can tell you're a little tense,
so I'm just gonna give you a little personal space!
Rabbit, whatever you do,
do not let go!
- I'm gonna let go!
- You're gonna to what?
One, two...
Carrots, you saved my life.
Well, that's what we do at the ZPD...
Awww...
Well, this should be good.
I thought this was just a missing mammal case,
but it's way bigger.
Mr. Otterton did not just disappear.
I believe he and this jaguar,
they...
They went savage, sir.
Savage? This isn't the stone age, Hopps.
Animals don't go savage.
I thought so too.
Till I saw this.
What?
He was right here!
The savage jaguar?
Sir, I know what I saw.
He almost killed us!
Or maybe any agressive predator
looks savage to rabbits?
Let's go!
Wait! Sir!
I'm not the only one who saw him.
You think I'm gonna believe a fox?
Well, he was a key witness, and I...
Two days to find the otter,
or you quit.
That was the deal.
Badge.
- But, sir, we had...
- Badge!
Uh, no.
- What did you say, fox?
- Sorry, what I said was "no...".
She will not be giving you that badge.
Look, you gave her a clown vest,
and a three-wheeled joke-mobile,
and two days to solve a case
you guys haven't cracked in two weeks?
Yeah, it's no wonder she needed
to get help from a fox.
None of you guys were gonna help her,
were you?
Here's the thing, chief.
You gave her the 48 hours,
so technically we still have...
ten left to find our Mr. Otterton.
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
So if you'll excuse us, we have a very
big lead to follow and a case to crack.
Good day.
Officer Hopps.
Thank you.
Never let them see that they get to you.
So...
Things do get to you?
I mean not, not anymore.
But I was small and emotionally
unbalanced like you once.
- Har har.
- No, it's true.
I think I was 8, or maybe 9...
And all I wanted to do was join
the Junior Ranger Scouts.
So my mom scaped together enough money
to buy me a brand new uniform.
Because, by god, I
was gonna fit in.
Even if I was the only predator
in the troop, the only fox.
I was gonna be part of a pack.
- Ready for initiation?
- Yeah. Pretty much born ready.
I was so proud.
Okay. Now raise your right
paw, and deliver the oath.
I, Nicholas Wilde, promise to be brave,
loyal, helpful and trustworthy.
Even though you're a fox?
What?
No, no! What did I
do wrong, you guys?
No, please! What did I do wrong?
What did I do?
If you thought we would ever
trust a fox without a muzzle?
You're even dumber than you look.
Is he gonna cry?
I learned two things that day.
One:
I was never gonna let anyone
see that they got to me.
And two?
If the world's only gonna see
a fox as shifty and untrustworthy...
There's no point in trying
to be anything else.
Nick, you are so much more than that.
Boy, look at that
traffic down there.
How about we go up to
Chuck in traffic central?
Chuck, how are things looking
on the jam cams?
Nick, I'm glad you told me.
The jam cams...
- Seriously, it's okay.
- No, no no!
There are traffic cameras everywhere.
All over the canopy!
- Whatever happened to that jaguar...
- The traffic cameras would have caught it!
- Bingo!
- Ho-ho! Pretty sneaky, slick!
However, if you didn't have
access to the system before,
I doubt chief Buffalo Butt is
gonna let you into it now.
No. But I have a friend
at City Hall who might.
Eh. Sir, if we could just review
these very important billings.
Sir! Oh, I'm sorry.
Sir.
Okay! I heard you, Bellwether,
just take care of it!
Please.
And clear my afternoon, I'm going out.
Oh, no, no. But, sir, you do
have a meeting with
Herds and Gradings.
Sir, that's just, oh...
Oh, mutton chops.
Assistant Mayor Bellwether,
we need your help.
OFFICE OF THE
ASSISTANT
MAYOR
(PLEASE KNOCK!)
We just need to get into
the traffic cam database.
- So fluffy!
- Hey!
- Sheep never let me get this close!
- You can't just touch a sheep's wool!
- It's like cotton candy.
- Stop it!
Where to?
Ah... Rainforest Dsitrict.
Vine and Tujunga.
There.
Traffic cams for the whole city.
This is so exiting actually.
I mean, well, you know.
I never get to do
anything this important.
But you're the assistant mayor of Zootopia.
Oh.
I'm more of a glorified secretary.
I think Mayor Lionheart just
wanted the sheep vote.
But he did give me that nice mug.
WORLD'S GREATEST
ASSISTANT MAYOR (Written with marker)
DAD (Crossed out)
Feels good to be appreciated.
Smellwether!
Ah.
That's a fun little name he likes to use.
I called him Lionfart once,
he did not care for that.
Let me tell you, it was
not a good day for me.
- Yes, sir.
- I thought you were gonna cancel my afternoon.
Oh, dear. I better go.
Let me know what you find.
It was really nice for me to be...
While we're young, Smellwether.
You think when she goes
to sleep she counts herself?
Shush.
Okay, traffic cams..
Tujunga.... Tujunga....
We're in.
- Who are these guys?
- Eh. Timberwolves.
Look at these dum-dums.
Huh!
Bet you a nickel one of them's gonna howl.
And there it is.
I mean, what is it with wolves
and the howling, it's...?
Howlings!
Night Howlers!
That's what Manchas was afraid of, wolves!
The wolves are the Night Howlers!
- If they took Manchas..
- I bet they took Otterton too.
All we gotta do is find out
where they went.
Wait, where'd they go?
You know, if I wanted to avoid surveillance
because I was doing something illegal,
which I never have, I would use the
maintenance tunnel 6B.
Which would put them out...
right there.
Well, look at you, junior detective.
You know, I think you'd actually
make a pretty good cop.
Eh. How dare you.
Acacia Alley. Ficus Underpass.
South canyon.
Mm-hm.
They're heading out of town.
Where does that road go?
[ CLIFFSIDE ]
Gary, quit it!
You're gonna start a howl!
I didn't start it.
Come on.
You are a clever bunny.
It looks like this was a hospital.
You know, after you,
you're the cop.
Okay, all clear.
Ha.
All this equipment is brand new.
Carrots.
Claw marks.
Yeah, huge, huge claw marks.
What kind of...
Mr. Manchas.
It's him!
We found our otter.
Mr. Otterton, my name is Officer Judy Hopps.
Your wife sent me to find you.
We're gonna get you out of here now.
Or not.
Guess he's in no rush
to get home to the missus.
11, 12, 13, 14.
Not including Manchas,
it's... it's fourteen.
Chief Bogo handed out 14 missing mammal files.
They're all here...
All the missing mammals are right here.
Huh!
Enough!
I don't want excuses, doctor,
I want answers.
Mayor Lionheart, please.
We're doing everything we can.
Really?
Cause I got a dozen and a half animals here
who've gone off the rails crazy,
And you can't tell me why.
Now I'd call that awfully far
from doing everything!
Sir, it may be time to consider their biology.
What?
What do you mean "biology"?
The only animals going savage are predators.
We cannot keep it a secret.
We need to come forward.
Hm, great idea.
Tell the public.
And how do you think they're gonna feel
about their mayor who is a lion?!
- I'll be ruined!
- Well, what does Chief Bogo say?
Chief Bogo doesn't know. And we
are going to keep it that way.
Oh, no!
- Someone's here.
- Sir, you need to go. Now.
Security, sweep the area.
Great, we're dead.
We're dead. That's it. I'm dead.
You're dead. Everybody's dead.
- Can you swim?
- What?
Can I swim?
Yes, I can swim. Why?
Aaahhhh!
Carrots!
Hopps! Judy!
We gotta tell Bogo!
Wow, you are one hot dancer, Chief Bogo.
- Chief Bogo!
- Not now.
- Wait, is that Gazelle?
- No!
I'm Gazelle, and you
are one hot dancer.
You have the app too?
Ooohhh...  Chief!
Clawhauser! Can't you see I'm working
on the missing mammal cases?
Oh! Yes, of course.
About that, sir.
Officer Hopps just called,
she found all of them.
Wow, I'm impressed.
Mayor Lionheart, you have the right
to remain silent. Anything you...
You don't understand,
I was trying to protect the city!
You were just trying
to protect your job.
No, listen. We still don't
know why this is happening.
It could destroy Zootopia.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
Ladies and gentlemammals,
14 mammals went missing and
all 14 have been found...
by our newest recruit,
who will speak to you in a moment.
- I'm so nervous.
- Okay, press conference 101.
You wanna look smart, answer their question
with your own question
and then answer that question.
Like this: "Excuse me, Officer Hopps.
What can you tell us about the case?"
"Well, was this a tough case?
Yes, yes it was. You see?"
You should be
up there with me.
We did this together.
Well, am I a cop?
No. No, I am not.
Funny you should say that.
Because, well, I've been thinking.
It would be nice to have a partner.
Here. In case you need
something to write with.
Officer Hopps.
It's time.
So now, I'll turn things over to the officer
who cracked the case.
Officer Judy Hopps.
Yes?
What can you tell us about
the animals that went savage?
Well, the animals in question...
Emm.
Are they all different species?
Yes. Yes, they are.
Okay, so what is the connection?
Oh. All we know is that they are all
members of the predator family.
So predators are the
only ones going savage?
That is accu..
Yes, that is accurate, yes.
- Why? Why is this happening?
- We still don't know.
But, emm.
It may have something to do with biology.
What do you mean, biology?
A biological component.
You know, something in their DNA.
In their DNA,
can you elaborate on that, please?
Yes. What I mean is
thousands of years ago
Eh, predators survived through their...
agressive hunting instincts.
For whatever reason, they seem to be
reverting back to their primitive, savage ways.
Officer Hopps, could
it happen again?
It is possible.
So, we must be vigilant.
And we at the ZPD are prepered
and are here to protect you.
- Will more mammals go savage?
- What is being done to protect us?
Have you considered a mandatory
quarantine on predators?
Okay, thank you, Officer Hopps.
That's all the time that we have.
No more questions.
- Was I okay?
- Oh, you did fine.
That went so fast, I
didn't get a chance to
mention you or say anything
about how we...
Oh, I think you said plenty.
What do you mean?
"Clearly there's a
biological component?"
"These predators may be reverting back
to their primitive, savage ways?"
Are you serious?
I just stated the
facts of the case.
I mean, it's not like a
bunny could go savage.
Right, but a fox could? Huh?
- Nick, stop it, you're not like them.
- Oh, there's a 'them' now?
You know what I mean,
you're not that kind of predator.
The kind that needs
to be muzzled?
The kind that makes you think you need
to carry around fox repellant?
Yeah, don't think I didn't notice that
little item the first time we met.
Look. Let me ask you a question.
Are you afraid of me?
Do you think I might go nuts?
You think I might go savage?
You think I might try to eat you?
Huh!
I knew it, huh.
Just when I thought somebody
actually believed in me, huh?
Probably best if you don't have
a predator as a partner.
No, Nick.
Nick!
Officer Hopps, were you just
threatened by that predator?
No, he's my friend.
We can't even trust our own friends?
That is not what I said.
Please.
- Are we safe?
- Have any other foxes gone savage?
More bad news in this city gripped by fear.
A caribou is in critical condition.
The victim of a mauling by
a savage polar bear.
This, the 27th such attack,
comes just one week after ZPD Officer,
Judy Hopps connected the violence
to traditionally predatory animals.
Meanwhile, a peace rally organized by
popstar Gazelle was marred by protest.
- Go back to the forest, predator!
- I am from the savannah.
Zootopia is a unique place.
It's a crazy, beautiful, diverse city.
Where we celebrate our differences.
This is not the Zootopia I know.
The Zootopia I know
is better than this.
We don't just blindly assign blame.
We don't know why these
attacks keep happening.
But it's irresponsible to label all
predators as savages.
It's not my Emmitt.
We cannot let fear divide us.
Please give me back the Zootopia I love.
Come on, Hopps.
The new mayor wants to see us.
The mayor?
Why?
It would seem you've arrived.
Clawhauser?
What are you doing?
Uh. They thought it would be
better if a predator
such as myself wasn't the first face
that you see
when you walk into the ZPD.
What?
They're gonna move me to records.
It's downstairs.
It's by the boiler.
Hopps1
Integrity
Honesty
Bravery
Emm.
I don't understand.
Our city is 90% prey, Judy,
and right now
they're just really scared.
You're a hero to them.
They trust you.
And so that's why Chief Bogo and I
want you to be the public face of the ZPD.
I'm... not...
I'm not a hero.
I came here to make the world
a better place. But...
... I think I broke it.
Don't give yourself so much credit, Hopps.
The world has always been broken,
that's why we need good cops.
Like you.
With all due respect, sir,
a good cop is supposed to serve and protect.
Help the city.
Not tear it apart.
- I don't deserve this badge.
- Hopps.
Judy, you've worked so hard
to get here.
It's what you've wanted since
you were a kid.
You can't quit.
Thank you for the opportunity.
A dozen carrots.
Have a nice day.
Come on.
Hey there, Jude.
Jude the Dude.
Remember that one?
How we doing?
- I'm fine.
- You are not fine, your ears are droopy.
Why did I think I could
make a difference?
- Because you're a trier, that's why.
- You've always been a trier.
Oh, I tried.
And it made life so much worse
for so many innocent predators.
Oh, not all of them, though.
Speak of the devil. Right on time.
Is that Gideon Grey?
Yeah, it sure is.
We work with him now.
He's our partner. And we never
would have considered it,
- had you not opened our minds.
- That's right.
I mean, kid's turned into one of the
top pastry chefs in the tri-burrows.
That's...
That's really cool, you guys.
Gideon Grey. I'll be darned.
Hey, Judy. I'd just like to say I'm sorry
for the way I behaved in my youth.
I had a lot of self-doubt,
and it manifested itself
in the form of unchecked
rage and agression.
I was a major jerk.
Well, I know a thing or two
about being a jerk.
Anyhow, I brought you all these pies.
Hey, kids! Don't you run through that
midnicampum holicithias.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Well, now. There's a
four-dollar word, Mr. H.
My family always just
call them Night Howlers.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Oh.
Kid's talking about those flowers, Judy.
I use them to keep the bugs off the produce,
but I don't like the little ones going near them
on acoount of what happened
to your uncle Terry.
Yeah, Terry ate one whole when we were kids
and went completely nuts.
He bit the dickens out of your mother.
A bunny can go savage.
Savage? Well, that's a strong word.
But it did hurt like the devil.
Well, sure it did. There's a sizable
divot in your arm. I'd call that savage.
Night Howlers aren't wolves,
they're flowers.
The flowers are making the predators go savage.
That's it! That's what
I've been missing!
Oh, keys! Keys! Keys! Keys!
Hurry, come on!
Oh. Thank you!
I love you, bye!
- You catch any of that, Bon?
- Not one bit.
That makes me feel a little bit better,
I thought she was talking in
tongues or something.
Who is it?
I need to find Nick.
Please.
Nick?
Oh, Nick.
Night Howlers aren't wolves,
they're toxic flowers.
I think someone is targetting predators
on purpose and making them go savage.
Wow.
Isn't that interesting?
Wait, please don't..
I know you'll never forgive me.
And I don't blame you.
I wouldn't forgive me either.
It was ignorant, and irresponsible,
and small-minded.
But predators shouldn't suffer
because of my mistakes.
I have to fix this.
But I can't do it without you.
And...
And after we're done...
you can hate me.
And...
And that'll be fine.
Because I was a horrible
friend and I hurt you.
And you can walk away knowing
that you were right. All along.
I really am just a dumb bunny.
Don't worry, Carrots,
I'll let you erase it. In 48 hours.
All right, get in here.
Okay. Oh, you bunnies.
You're so emotional.
There we go, deep breath.
Are you-Are you just
trying to steal the pen?
Is that what this is?
- You are standing on my tail, though. Off, off!
- I'm sorry.
HOPPS
FAMILY FARM
I thought you guys only grew carrots.
Mmph.
- What's your plan?
- We are gonna follow the Night Howlers.
Okay, how?
- Know this guy?
- Uh-huh. I told you, I know everybody.
Ha-ha. Well, hello!
Step right up.
Anything you need, I got it.
All your favorite movies.
I've got movies that
haven't even been released yet.
Hey, 15% off.
20!
Make me an offer.
Come on!
Well, well, look who it is,
the Duke of Bootleg.
What's it to you, Wilde?
Shouldn't you be melting down
a Pawpsicle or something?
Hey, if it isn't
flopsy the copsie.
We both know those weren't only
onions I caught you stealing.
What were you gonna do with
those Night Howlers, Weselton?
It's Weaselton, Duke Weaselton.
And I ain't talking, rabbit.
And there ain't nothing
you can do to make me.
Ice him.
Ahhh!
Ho! Ho! Ho! Ah!
You dirty rat, why are you helping her?
She's a cop!
And the godmother to
my future granddaughter.
- I'm gonna name her Judy.
- Ohhhh...
Heh heh heh.
Ice this weasel.
Aww! All right, all right!
Please! I'll talk. I'll talk.
I stole the Night Howlers
so I could sell them.
They offered me what I
couldn't refuse: Money.
And to whom did you sell them?
A ram named Doug. We got
a drop spot underground.
Just watch it.
Doug is the opposite of friendly.
He's unfriendly.
Come on.
The weasel wasn't lying.
Yeah, it looks like old Doug's cornered
the market on Night Howlers.
You got Doug here.
What's the mark?
Cheetah in Sahara Square.
Got it.
Serious? Yeah, I know they're fast,
I can hit him.
Listen, I hit a tiny little otter
through the open window of a moving car.
Yeah, I'll buzz you when it's done.
Or you'll see it on the news.
You know, whichever comes first.
Hey, Doug, open up!
We've got your latte.
All right, Woolter and Jesse are back,
so I'm leaving now. Out.
Hey. Wait, where you going?
Where are you going? Get back here!
What are you doing?
He's gonna see you!
What are you looking at?
Hey!
Whatever you're thinking,
stop thinking it.
Carrots.
You better have the
extra foam this time.
HA!
Hey!
Open up!
What are you doing? You
just trapped us in here!
We need to get this
evidence to the ZPD.
- Okay, great. Here it is. Got it.
- No, all of it.
Wait, what?
Oh, great, you're a
conductor now, huh?
Hey. Listen. It would take a miracle
to get this rustbucket going.
Well.
Hallelujah.
We kinda got a situation at the lab.
It just got worse!
Mission accomplished.
Would it be premature for me to
do a little victory toot-toot?
All right.
One toot-toot.
Well, I can cross that off
the bucket list.
I may have to rescind
that victory toot-toot.
Maybe that's just hail.
Back off!
Incoming!
- Carrots!
- Don't stop! Keep going.
No, stop.
Please stop!
Do not stop this car!
Ahhh!
Owww!
Whoa!
- Speed up, Nick. Speed up!
- There's another train coming!
Trust me, speed up.
Stop the train!
Hey.
Need some help?
Oh, no. Oh, no no no.
Too fast! Too fast! Hold on!
I think this is our stop.
Okay, maybe...
Maybe some of the evidence survived.
Everything is gone.
We've lost it all.
Yeah. All, except for this.
Ah, ha ha ha ha!
- Ooh, Nick! Yes!
- Ow.
Come on!
We gotta get to the ZPD.
Cut through the Natural History Museum.
- There it is.
- Judy. Judy!
Mayor Bellwether.
We found out what's happening.
Someone's darting predators with a serum.
That's what's making them go savage.
I'm so proud of you, Judy.
You did just a super job.
Thank you, ma'am.
How did you know
where to find us?
I'll go ahead and
I'll take that case now.
You know what? I think Nick and I
will just take this to the ZPD.
- Run.
Get them!
Ah....
Carrots!
Aww.
Here, I got you.
Get in here.
Okay.
Now, just relax.
Whoops.
- Blueberry?
- Pass.
Come on out, Judy.
Take the case.
Get it to Bogo.
I'm not gonna leave you behind,
that's not happening.
- I can't walk.
- Just.. We'll think of something.
We're on the same team, Judy.
Underestimated.
Underappreciated.
Aren't you sick of it?
Predators.
They may be strong and loud.
But prey outnumber predators 10 to 1.
Think about it. 90% of the population
united against a common enemy.
We'll be unstoppable.
Huh?
Over there!
Oh!
Ah!
Well, you should have just
stayed on the carrot farm, huh?
It really is too bad,
I did like you.
What are you gonna do?
Kill me?
Oohhh.
No, of course not.
He is.
No!
Oh, Nick?
Yes, police! There's a savage fox in the
Natural History Museum!
Officer Hopps is down.
Please hurry!
No, Nick.
Don't do this. Fight it.
Oh, but he can't help it.
Can he?
Since predators are just biologically
predisposed to be savages.
Get back!
Gosh!
Think of the headline!
Hero Cop Killed by Savage Fox.
So that's it? Prey fears predator,
and you stay in power?
Yeah.
Pretty much.
It won't work.
Fear always works.
And I'll dart every predator in
Zootopia to keep it that way.
Ah!
Oh, Nick.
No.
Bye-bye, bunny.
Blahhh...
Blood, blood, blood!
And death.
All right, you know you're milking it.
Besides, I think we got it.
I think we got it.
We got it up there,
thank you, yakety-yak.
You laid it all out beautifully.
What?
Yeah. Oh, are-are you looking for the serum?
Well, it's right here.
What you've got
in the weapon there,
those are blueberries,
from my family's farm.
Mmmuch. They are delicious.
You should try some.
I framed Lionheart,
I can frame you too.
It's my word against yours.
Ooo.
Actually...
And I'll dart every predator
in Zootopia to keep it that way.
- It's your word against yours.
- Huh?
It's called a hustle, Sweetheart.
Boom!
Former mayor, Dawn Bellwether
is behind bars today,
guilty of masterminding the savage attacks
that have plagued Zootopia of late.
Her predecessor, Leodore Lionheart,
denies any knowledge of her plot,
claiming he was just trying
to protect the city.
Did I falsely imprison those animals?
Well, yes.
Yes, I did.
It was a classic doing the wrong thing
for the right reason kind of a deal.
In related news, doctors say the Night Howlers'
antidote is proving effective
in rehabilitating the afflicted predators.
Oh, Emmitt!
Thank you.
When I was a kid,
I thought Zootopia was this perfect place.
Where everyone got along,
and anyone could be anything.
Turns out, real life is a little bit more
complicated than a slogan on a bumper sticker.
Real life is messy.
We all have limitations.
We all make mistakes.
Which means, hey, glass half full,
we all have a lot in common.
And the more we try to
understand one another.
The more exceptional each of us will be.
But we have to try.
So no matter what type
of animal you are.
From the biggest elephant,
to our first fox.
I implore you.
Try.....
Try to make the world a better place.
OFFICER
Nicholas P. Wilde
Look inside yourself and recognize
that change starts with you.
It starts with me.
It starts with all of us.
- Yeh!
All right, all right, enough.
Shut it!
We have some new recruits
with us this morning.
Including our first fox.
Who cares.
Hah. You should have your own line
of inspirational greeting cards, sir.
Shut your mouth, Wilde.
Assignments.
Officers Grizzoli, Fragmire, Delgato.
Tundratown SWAT.
Snarlov, Higgins, Wolfard.
Undercover.
Hopps, Wilde.
Parking duty.
Dismissed.
Just kidding!
We have reports of a street racer
tearing up Savannah Central.
Find him.
Shut him down.
So are all the rabbits bad drivers,
or is it just you?
Oops.
Sorry.
Heh heh.
Sly bunny.
Dumb fox.
You know you love me.
Do I know that?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Sir, you were going 115 miles per hour,
I hope you have a good explanation.
Flash, Flash.
Hundred Yard Dash!
Nick...
Good evening, Zootopia!
Come on, everybody.
Put your paws up.
♪ I messed up tonight ♪
♪ I lost another fight ♪
♪ I still mess up but I'll just start again ♪
♪ I keep falling down ♪
♪ I keep on hitting the ground ♪
♪ I always get up now to see what's next ♪
♪ I won’t give up,  ♪
♪ no I won’t give in ♪
♪ Till I reach the end ♪
♪ And then I’ll start again ♪
♪ Though I’m on the lead ♪
♪ I wanna try everything ♪
♪ I wanna try even though I could fail ♪
♪ I won’t give up,  ♪
♪ no I won’t give in ♪
♪ Till I reach the end ♪
♪ And then I’ll start again ♪
♪ No I won't leave ♪
♪ I wanna try everything ♪
♪ I wanna try even though I could fail ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Try everything ♪
Subtitle edited by - Aorion -
Corrections by Shincosutan.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7j8bb
Help other users to choose the best subtitles